爆炸性新聞字幕
Subtitles by explosiveskull
沒人像我一樣吸毒嗎
Ain't nobody dope as me
我穿得很新鮮，很乾淨
I'm dressed so fresh, so clean
那麼新鮮，那麼乾淨，乾淨
So fresh and so clean, clean
你不覺得我很性感嗎？
Don't you think I'm so sexy?
我穿得很新鮮，很乾淨...
I'm dressed so fresh, so clean...
哦，我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
來吧。夥計！
Come on. Man!
我穿得很新鮮，很乾淨...
I'm dressed so fresh, so clean...
我不知道這些東西
I don't know this stuff
那還不算近
That's not even close
不
No
泰迪！晚餐，寶貝！
Teddy! Dinner, baby!
你父親在等著呢！
Your father's waiting!
在閣樓上創造的，我們是最酷的母親...
Created in the attic, we are the coolest mother...
你什麼意思，你在抗議
What do you mean, you're protesting
國家成就測試？
the State Achievement Test?
聽起來好像有人沒有準備好
Sounds like someone's unprepared
我準備好了
I am prepared Mmm
站起來
To take a stand
pops，那些標準化測試
Pops, those standardized tests
有文化偏見
are culturally biased
他們要我計算海牛的平均數量
They want me to calculate the average number of manatees
在佛羅里達
that are in Florida
這有什麼關係
What does that have to do
非洲裔美國人的經歷？
with the African-American experience?
你聽到了嗎，格拉迪斯？
You hear that, Gladys?
我們請路易斯·法拉漢部長出席了會議
We got Minister Louis Farrakhan at the table
你知道嗎，泰迪？
You know what, Teddy?
上次我檢查的時候，
The last time I checked,
你雙胞胎妹妹丹尼斯是黑人，
your twin sister Denise here is black,
她在練習測試中得了1500分
and she pulled a 1500 on the practice test
那實際上是1540年，爸爸啊！
It was actually a 1540, Daddy Ah!
你去吧，女孩。那是我的孩子
You go, girl. That's my baby
只是做我最擅長的事情，而不是泰迪的屁股
Just doing what I do best outshining Teddy's butt
泰迪熊，這到底是怎麼回事？
What's this really all about, Teddy Bear?
嗯？
Hmm?
你需要幫助嗎？
Do you need help?
這就是一切嗎？
Is that what this is all about?
我不知道，媽媽
I don't know, Mommy
我是說
I mean
也許我確實需要幫助
maybe I do need help
隨便看看這本該死的學習書
Help yourself to the goddamn study book
見鬼，你簽了名就可以得到400分
Hell, you get 400 points just for signing your name
你知道怎麼拼寫你的名字，是嗎？
You do know how to spell your name, don't you?
東-西-東...什麼？
T-H-E... What?
你錯了
You're wrong
我的名字裡沒有H
Ain't no H in my name
她在拼寫你的合法名字
She's spelling your legal name
西奧多。
Theodore.
好吧，這就是400分
Well, there goes those 400 points
她在學校喜歡一個中國男孩
She like a Chinese boy at school
閉上你的餡餅洞！
Shut your pie hole!
大家都坐下
Everyone take a seat
東-西-東
T-H-E
別看他斯圖爾特是個混蛋
Don't even look at him Stewart's an asshole
好的，學生們，請打破你們考試冊上的封條
Okay, students, please break the seal on your test books
開始吧
and begin
完成的
Done
你完成了整個測試？
You finished the whole test?
不，我不幹了
No, I'm done with this
我完了！
I'm finished!
你覺得我像只綿羊嗎，馬爾夫？
Do I look like a sheep to you, Marv?
不
No
你們都可以繼續當綿羊
You all can continue to be sheep
我不會成為任何人的羊
I'm not gonna be nobody's sheep
沃克先生
Mr. Walker
我不知道該怎麼做
I don't know how
製造噪音，但是你知道我想說什麼
to make the noise, but you know what I'm trying to say
你們都可以繼續墜入愛河
Y'all can keep falling for the
如果你想的話，
for the man's plan if you want to,
但是你們最終都會欠下愚蠢的學生債務
but y'all gonna end up in stupid student debt
你看起來已經是壞信用了
You look like bad credit already
這整部分就在這裡
This whole section right here
帶著你破屁股的探索牌的氣味
reeks of Discover cards, with your broke ass
我會成為贏家，我會成功
I'm gonna be a winner I'm gonna succeed
在生活的學校裡，做真正的事情
in the school of life, doing real stuff
我要給我買一輛真正的飛行車，
I'm gonna get me a real fly car,
我會有一個好女孩
and I'm gonna have me a nice girl
你們都過不去了
Y'all ain't gonna make it
泰德，出去！
Ted, get out!
丹尼斯的奶頭上有頭髮
Denise got hair on her titties
貓從包裡出來了
Cat's out of the bag
出去！你讓我們很尷尬！
Get out! You're embarrassing us!
你們都是些綿羊！
Y'all some sheep!
你們都是羊！
Y'all sheep!
面對你！
In your face!
哈哈，笨蛋
Ha-ha, stupid
現在我要在麵團裡打滾
Now I'm gonna be rolling in the dough
順便說一句，丹尼斯
And by the way, Denise
我認為丹尼斯有令人難以置信的乳頭
I think Denise has incredible titties
馬伕，閉嘴！
Marv, shut up!
嘿，吉姆，你認識他們老甜心爸爸
Hey, Jim, you know them old sugar daddies
他們在欺騙，他們告訴他們女孩
They be trickin', they tell them girls
我說過你可以的
I said you could have
不管你喜歡什麼，如果你喜歡
Whatever you like, if you like
我說過你可以的
I said you could have
不管你喜歡什麼，如果你喜歡
Whatever you like, if you like
是的，是的，甲板上的煙囪
Yeah, yeah, stacks on deck
冰面上的帕隆
Patron on ice
我們可以整夜開瓶子
And we can pop bottles all night
寶貝，你可以
And, baby, you could have
不管你喜歡什麼，如果你喜歡
Whatever you like, if you like
我說過你可以的
I said you could have
不管你喜歡什麼，如果你喜歡
Whatever you like, if you like
是的，寶貝，我可以對你這麼特別，這麼好
Yeah, baby, I could treat you so special, so nice
今晚給你的飛機加油，寶貝，你可以走了
Gas up a jet for you tonight and, baby, you could go
不管你喜歡什麼地方，如果你喜歡
Wherever you like, if you like
我說過你可以的
I said you could have
不管你喜歡什麼，如果你喜歡，是的
Whatever you like, if you like, yeah
任何時候你想，拿起電話
Any time you want to, pick up the telephone
你知道丟幾堆沒什麼...
You know it ain't nothin to drop a couple stacks...
這個項目接管了我的生活
This project has taken over my life
來吧，上帝，我等不及要睡覺了
Come on God, I can't wait to sleep
來這裡
Come here
謝謝，寶貝，沒問題
Thank you, baby No problem
哦，今晚我太緊張了
Oh, I'm so nervous about tonight
感謝上帝你來了
Thank God you're coming
你為什麼緊張？
Why are you nervous?
莉斯，你做得很棒
Lis, you did an amazing job
你會殺了這個
You're gonna kill this
將會是亞特蘭大最熱的地方
Gonna be the hottest spot in Atlanta
行
Okay
威爾，嗯，可愛的瑪雅人
Will, uh will the lovely Maya
今晚也要加入我們嗎？
be joining us this evening as well?
我不喜歡他
I don't like him
廚師克萊蒙邀請了我的整個團隊
Chef Clemont invited my entire team
今晚吃飯，所以要乖，好嗎？
to dinner tonight, so be nice, okay?
是的，也許要讚美她
Yes Maybe try to compliment her
好吧，愛你
Okay Love you
好吧。再見，愛你。祝你愉快
Okay. Bye Love you. Have a good day
嘿瑪雅！
Hey, Maya!
嗨，泰迪
Hey, Teddy
今天有人看起來非常迷人
Somebody looks extremely attractive today
謝謝你
Thank you
我不是以同樣的眼光看著你
Not that I'm looking at you the same way
我看著我的女人，因為我不會那樣做
I look at my woman, because I wouldn't do that
我們走吧。我們走吧
Let's just go. Let's go
我喜歡編織！泰迪！
I love the weave! Teddy!
或者假髮。無論哪個
Or the wig. Whichever
這是我的頭髮
This is my hair
你做到了，噓停下來
You did that, boo Stop
我要停下來
I'm just going to stop
你明白我想做什麼嗎
You get what I'm trying to do
他嫉妒你的美貌
He's jealous of your beauty
我搞砸了
I blew it
我肯定搞砸了
I definitely blew that
我踏上了新的春天...
I got a new spring in my step...
哦，看，泰迪來了
Oh, look, there's Teddy
泰迪！喲，泰迪！
Teddy! Yo, Teddy!
看起來不錯
It's looking pretty good
在前面
Up ahead
我的名字叫泰迪，我是來製作的
My name is Teddy, and I am here to make
你燒烤的夢想成真了
your barbecue dreams come true
埃斯特，你是個小女人，
Now, Esther, you're a small woman,
但是我知道你有一顆大心，
but I know you have a big heart,
這就是為什麼我向你推薦大鋼鐵
which is why I recommend the Big Steel for you
沒有多少女人能承受這麼多的鋼鐵，
Not a lot of women can take this much steel,
但是我知道你可以嗯！
but I know you can Mmm!
皮特布爾，嗯？
The Pitbull, huh?
美洲駝？
□Como te llamas?
我駱駝皮布爾
Me llamo Pitbull
戴爾!
!Dale!
你不是西班牙人，是嗎？
You're not Spanish, are you?
莫裡斯，我能從你的眼睛裡看到它
I can see it in your eyes, Morris
但是我也可以告訴你妻子
But I can also tell that your wife
你知道，你妻子不在同一個頁面上
you know, your wife isn't on the same page
我的意思是，這並不完全像她
I mean, it's not like she completely
控制錢包
controls the purse strings
享受吧
Enjoy it
不要讓我失望
Don't you let me down
你最好停下來，夥計
You better stop it, man
你不開始嗎
Don't you start that
那是一個大師班
That was a master class
我不能讓鮑比·弗萊買那頭野獸
I couldn't get Bobby Flay to buy that beast
你知道嗎？有一次我看到那個男人的錢包，
You know what? Once I saw the man purse,
那傢伙在我手裡油膩膩的，他真的是
the guy was putty in my hands He really was
泰迪，我只是想讓你知道
Teddy, I just want you to know
你就像我從未有過的兒子
you are like the son I never had
好吧，我的意思是，來吧，你有喬·朱尼爾
Well, I mean, come on, you got Joe Junior
嗯，是的，但是他是我的兒子，
Well, yeah, but he's the son I do have,
我只是沒有那麼瘋狂
and I'm just not all that crazy about it
我是說，看看他
I mean, look at him
但是我的觀點是這些年前，
But my point is this all those years ago,
我碰上了一個滿臉青春痘的少年
I took a chance on a pimply-faced teenager
我的小加裡·科爾曼
My little Gary Coleman
我的小韋伯斯特
My little Webster
結果對我們倆來說都很棒
And it turned out great for both of us
所以我決定，當我退休的時候
So I've decided, when I retire
我要去燒烤城
I'm turning Barbecue City
超過...敬你
over... to you
對不起？
Excuse me?
什麼？
What?
呃，不要——不要操我
Uh, don't-don't shit me
我是認真的
I'm serious
哦，我的上帝，喬
Oh, my God, Joe
我只是起了雞皮疙瘩
I just got-got goose bumps
是的！我渾身起雞皮疙瘩
Yes! I got goose bumps all over
我不知道該說什麼，夥計，謝謝你
I don't know what to say, man Thank you
不，謝謝
No. Thank you
兒子
son
喬，你在說什麼？
What you talkin' 'bout, Joe?
你得過來，德拉蒙德先生
You gotta come here, Mr. Drummond
來這裡
Come here
都是你的，泰迪
All yours, Teddy
你怎麼想呢?哦
What do you think? Oh
太棒了
It's amazing
真的嗎？是
Really? Yeah
但是作為你的非官方財務顧問，
But as your unofficial financial advisor,
我有義務告訴你
I'm obligated to tell you
這枚戒指超出了你的預算
that this ring is way out of your budget
放鬆
Relax
麗莎很酷
Lisa's cool as hell
她知道你是誰
She knows who you are
麗莎不知道我是誰
Lisa does not know who I am
麗莎知道我是一名成功的烤肉推銷員
Lisa knows that I'm a successful barbecue salesman
馬文知道泰迪高中輟學
Marvin knows that Teddy's a high school dropout
那是一份又一份的生活薪水
that's living paycheck to paycheck
因為我和一個遠遠超過我體重的女人在一起
cause I'm with a woman that's way above my weight class
你的生活是建立在一個由卡片組成的金融機構之上的
Your life is built on a financial house of cards
停下保時捷，雙面人
Stop it The Porsche, the duplex
你想證明什麼？
What are you trying to prove?
另外，每次我們出去，
Plus, every single time we go out,
她提出支付支票
she offers to pay for the check
我讓她放下塑料的那天
The day that I let her put down her plastic
是我失去她的那一天
is the day that I lose her
你知道我不知道我為什麼這麼緊張
And you know that I don't know why I was so nervous
一起來了嘿
It's coming together Hey
嗨，麗莎
Hi Lisa
嗨！比安弗尼
Hi! Bienvenue
夥計，麗莎是我經歷過的最好的事情
Dude, Lisa's the best thing that ever happened to me
我不想搞砸這個，夥計
I don't want to mess this one up, man
我告訴他們是他幹的
I told them He did
他真的這麼說了
He actually said that
看那個
Ooh Look at that
看起來很棒一些甜點
That looks amazing Some dessert
哇。謝謝你
Wow Wow. Thank you
嗯。-非常感謝克萊蒙大廚也說
Mmm. - Thank you so much Chef Clemont also said
沒有支票
that there will be no check
這全在他身上
This is all on him
哇，我知道他會試試這個
Wow I knew he would try this
你知道嗎？告訴他我很感激，
You know what? Tell him I appreciate it,
但是我堅持付錢好嗎
but I insist on paying Okay
好吧，好吧，等等
Yeah Okay, well, just wait
等等，親愛的
Well, hold on, now, honey
親愛的，你不想冒犯他
Honey, you don't want to offend him
你是他的客人，對吧？
You're his guest, right?
相信我，你從來沒有從客戶那裡免費吃一頓飯
Trust me, you never take a free meal from a client
這樣，你就不欠他們任何東西了
That way, you don't owe them anything
這是真的謝謝你，麗莎
That's true Thank you, Lisa
我很感激你知道嗎
I appreciate it You know
嗯，只要你準備好了
Um Whenever you're ready
謝謝你
Thank you
你知道嗎？你知道嗎，寶貝？
You know what? You know what, then, baby?
如果是這樣，親愛的，那就讓我來
If that's the case, sweetie, then let me
不，寶貝，這是我的東西
No. Baby, this is my thing
我們有八個人我懂了
There's like eight of us I got it
你可以把它註銷，對吧？是
You can probably write it off, right? Yes
我沒有想到這是商業開支
I didn't think about that It is a business expense
好吧。-是啊，來吧
Okay. - Yeah Come on
W - W -等待，等待等待等待等待，LIS
W-W-Wait, wait Hold-hold up, Lis
這是商業開支，但是，李斯
It is a business expense, but, Lis
很明顯，泰迪真的想請客
it's clear that Teddy really wants to treat
我們都在這裡慶祝你，所以讓他來吧
We're all here celebrating you, so let him
對吧，泰迪？
Right, Teddy?
是
Yes
魔獸世界
Wow
是的。為什麼我們不更近？
Yes. Wh-Why aren't we closer?
因為你抓到我了
'Cause you get me
嗯
Mmm
我有。我明白了
I have it. I got it
我愛你愛你
I love you Love you back
黑色愛情
Black love
行
Okay
哦，媽的
Oh, shit
好吧，馬文，打我
All right, Marvin, hit me
謝謝你
Thank you
這是我最喜歡的事情之一，他做了
This is so good One of my favorite things that he does
那個焦糖餡餅，他以此聞名
That caramel tart, he's known for it All right
哦，我得進去
Oh, I gotta get in that
肯定會試試的
Definitely gonna try that
呃
Uh-uh
太神奇了，這些不是很漂亮嗎？
So amazing Aren't these beautiful?
他做這些只是為了我們真的嗎？
He did these just for us Really?
是的，你應該嘗嘗這個焦糖
Yeah You should try this caramel
我要去...我要吃一點
I'm gonna... I'm gonna take a little bit of it
進去帶我過去...帶我過去
Get in there Take me through... take me through
麗莎，帶我過去，這是一把椅子
Lisa, take me through So this is a chair
筆直向上，這是一把椅子
Straight up, it's a chair
我知道那麼多，但我能知道些什麼...給我
I know that much, but what tell me about... give me
椅子背後的音樂
the Behind the Music about the chair
假裝我在VH1或類似的地方
Pretend I'm on VH1 or something like that
事實上，這些椅子有一個非常有趣的故事
Well, actually, these chairs have a very interesting story
他們來自丹麥
They're from Denmark
在倉庫裡發現的
Found them in a warehouse Whoa
世紀中葉，現代，有點圓
Mid-century, modern, kind of rounded
是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
我知道它是藍色的
I know it's blue and
我不知道你這麼喜歡椅子
I didn't know you were so into chairs
哦，你不會相信我會回家，
Oh, you would not believe I'll go home,
我看看我的椅子，一會兒我就被打開了
I'll look at my chair, I get turned on in a second
這只是一種奇怪的戀物癖，你會喜歡這些，因為
It's just a weird fetish You would love these because
我不知道你是否注意到了藍寶石
I don't know if you noticed the cerulean kind of
壁紙的底色
undertone of the wallpaper Woof
但是我們有點想把它們綁在一起，
but we kind of wanted to tie it all together,
抵消了更硬、更直的線，
to kind of offset the harder, more straighter lines,
那是什麼？i
and What is that? I
我在意大利發現了這種面料，百分之百
I found this fabric in Italy It's 100%
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
哦，我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
不不不！什麼？
No, no, no! What?
先生，甜點有問題嗎？
Is there a problem with the dessert, sir?
我想那是蛋糕裡的陰毛
I think that's pubic hair in the cake
哦，我的上帝哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God Oh, my gosh
這陰毛在我該死的甜點裡嗎？
Is this pubic hair in my damn dessert?
我可以嗎？
May I?
對不起，什麼？我可以接受嗎？
I'm sorry, what? May I please take it?
真的，我告訴你是什麼
Literally, I'm telling you what it is
呃
Uh
這太多陰毛了
This is way too many pubes
這是什麼意思？
What does that mean?
我的意思是，一個太多陰毛了
I mean, one is too many pubes
如果你能告訴廚師
If you could tell the chef
謝謝你。謝謝你為我們處理這件事
Thank you. Thank you for taking care of this for us
我相信這些是你種的
I believe you planted these
不，不，不，不，你剛才說什麼？
No, no, no What'd you just say?
停下來。我明白了，你瘋了
Stop. I got this That's insane of you
我認識這個人一輩子了
I've known this man my entire life
他不是酒吧種植者，先生，不，不，不
He's not a pube planter, sir No, no, no
停下，馬伕。停下，也許是你種的
Stop, Marv. Stop Maybe you planted them
什麼？繁榮
What? Boom
我冒著生命危險來到這個國家
I risked my life coming to this country
所以我可以在某個隨意的傢伙的芝士蛋糕上種植陰毛？
so I can plant pubes on some random guy's cheesecake?
我不知道你喜歡什麼，夥計
I don't know what you're into, man
我有個消息要告訴你，夥計們
And I have a flash of news for you, guy
我在下面看風景好嗎
I man-scape down here Okay
那是我的女人，太多信息了
That's my woman, and that's too much information
這些是陰毛
And these are the pubes
一個非洲裔美國人
of an African-American guy
哦，該死什麼？這是種族主義，夥計
Oh, shit What? That's racist, man
這是描述性的
It's descriptive
描述性的，我的屁股。那是種族主義者路易斯？
Descriptive, my ass. That's racist Luis?
這就是非洲陰毛
That's what they are Afro pubes
朋友，朋友，發生了什麼？
Friends, friends, what is happening?
發生什麼事了？
What is happening?
陰毛與種族主義
Pubes and racism
克萊蒙大廚
Chef Clemont
好吧？我去拿
Mm-hmm All right? I go to take
一口我的芝士蛋糕
a bite of my cheesecake
看起來是陰毛
There's what appears to be pubic hair
在我的蛋糕裡
in my cake
他用他的
That he planted with his
非裔美國人的短髮型
African-American short-and-curlies
再說一遍非洲裔美國人，
Say African-American again,
我- -你的屁股變得又黑又捲曲！
and I'm-a get dark and curly in your ass!
我會再說一遍！好吧，再說一遍！
I will say it again! All right, say it again!
請大家冷靜下來
Please, everyone, calm down
我為此感到羞愧，我很抱歉，各位
I am mortified by this I am so sorry here, everyone
呃，我請客不
Uh, the meal is on me No
這就是他想要的
This is what he wants
路易斯，我需要在廚房和你談談謝謝
Luis, I need to speak to you in the kitchen Thank you
去廚房，夥計
Go in the kitchen, man
你會死的
You're going to die
路易斯，我需要在廚房和你談談
Luis, I need to speak to you in the kitchen
你找錯人了
You messed with the wrong guy
路易斯，現在
Luis, right now
現在你最好走了
Right now You better go
好吧，寶貝，就這樣
Okay, baby, just
你最好走！
You better go!
一定是在跟我開玩笑，廚師，
Gotta be kidding me Chef, please,
他一直是我，呃...我不想捲入其中
he's been I, uh... I don't want to get into it
感覺我周圍像是一團種族歧視
Feel like it's a cloud of racism around me
泰迪，怎麼回事？
Teddy, what is going on?
今晚我們沒有足夠的驚喜嗎？
Haven't we had enough surprises tonight?
我向你保證
Well, I promise you
這個值得，好嗎？
that this one will be worth it, okay?
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
這是什麼？
What's all this?
好吧，我會告訴你發生了什麼
Well, I will tell you what's going on
聽聽這個
So, listen to this
喬今天告訴我，當他退休的時候
Joe told me today that when he retires
他把這一切都留給我了
he's leaving all of this to me
寶貝，這太神奇了，我的意思是，這改變了生活
Baby, that's amazing I mean, it's life-changing
是的，也許你可以
Yeah And maybe you could
觸摸這個地方，改變設計，
put your touch on this place, change the design,
幫助把它帶到下一個層次？
help take it to the next level?
我為你感到驕傲。是
I'm so proud of you. Yeah
也許我們會擴張？是
Maybe we expand? Yes
特許經營，甚至？是
Franchise, even? Yeah
是的。哦，是的
Yes. Oh, yeah
寶貝，我們可以在這個地方做很多事情
Baby, we-we could do a lot with this place
首先，我們可以改變標誌
First of all, we could change the logo
燒烤之國。燒烤之旅。
Barbecue Nation. Barbecue Safari.
我的意思是，我們可以做很多事情
I mean, there are so many things we could do
老實說，我有很多想法
Honestly, I have so many ideas
i
I
我只知道有你在我身邊，
I just know that with you by my side,
任何事情都是可能的
that anything is possible
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
是嗎？
Yes Yes?
是的！是的！是嗎？
Yes! Yes! Yes?
嗯
Mmm
嗯，嗯
Mmm, mmm
等等，戒指。這裡
Wait, the ring. Here
你得戴上戒指
You gotta put the put the ring on
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
我喜歡，那我們慶祝一下吧
I love it Let's celebrate, then
嗯？你知道我得買些香檳哦，我的天
Huh? You know I had to get some champagne Oh, my God
我說，看，呃，我的寶寶會喜歡的。
I said, Look, uh, my baby gonna like it.
讓我給我的未婚妻來點香檳let me get some champagne for my fiancee
Let me pour some champagne for my fiancee
訂婚了。
Fiancee.
好吧，讓我們舉杯慶祝
All right, let's make a toast
對我們
To us To us
寶貝？嗯？
Baby? Hmm?
你聞到煤氣味了嗎？
Do you smell gas?
我很緊張，寶貝
I was nervous, babe
我不知道你會聞到我試圖聞到的味道
I didn't know you'd smell it I tried to
不，那是，嗯
No, that's, um
實際的...比如丙烷？
Actual... like, the propane?
你為什麼不站在外面，
Why don't you go stand outside,
我會把所有東西都放在這裡，我會帶你回家
I'll situate everything in here, and I'll get you home
好吧，愛你
Okay Love you
準備好
Be ready
嗯
Mm-hmm
所以，夥計們
So, guys
我可愛的小泰迪熊剛剛提出了這個問題
my sweet little Teddy Bear just popped the question
大驚喜
And big surprise
我答應了！
I said yes!
媽的！
Shit!
哦，媽的。哦，媽的！
Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
哦，上帝！嬰兒
Oh, God! Baby
泰迪，你沒事吧？
Teddy, are you okay?
我需要你告訴我未婚妻
I need you to tell my fiancee there's
發生了一起事故
there's been an accident
寶貝，是我
Baby, it's me
你能看見我嗎？泰迪？
Can you see me? Teddy?
我是你的未婚妻
I'm your fiancee
好的
Good
我出事了
I've been in an accident
哦，寶貝
Oh, baby
所以，喬沒有保險？
So, Joe didn't have insurance?
是的，他當然有，馬伕
Yeah, of course he did, Marv
他拿錢跑到佛羅里達去了
He took the money and ran off to Florida
夥計，我一直在到處找工作，夥計
Dude, I've been looking for a job everywhere, man
但是沒有像樣的銷售工作
But there are no decent sales jobs for
燒烤城最佳員工
an Employee of the Month at Barbecue City
我們會在這裡僱用你，但是你需要得到你的GED
We'd hire you here, but you need to get your GED
想想看，這些傢伙扯淡客戶
Think about it These guys bullshit clients
一整天都在談論他們不瞭解的資金
all day about funds they don't understand
你是天生的
You would be a natural
所以你是說如果我畢業了
So you're saying that if I graduated
高中畢業後，你能在這裡給我找份工作嗎？是
from high school, that then you could get me a job here? Yeah
但是你討厭學校，那我們為什麼還要上學呢
But you hate school, so why are we even having
這個對話？不，不，不，我不說話
this conversation? No, no, no. I'm not talking
關於上學
about going to school
我在說我的GED
I'm talking about getting my GED
這是不同的
And that's different
看，為了得到我的GED，
See, to get my GED,
我要做的就是去學校，
all I gotta do is go to the school,
稍微迷住校長
charm the principal a little bit
對吧？得到我想要的
Right? Get what I want Yeah
這是我的GED聽起來很簡單，Marv
Which is my GED Sounds pretty easy to me, Marv
如果你拿到了GED，嗯？
If you got your GED Huh?
我可能會給你掛電話
I could probably hook you up
聽我說，儘管停下來。停下，好嗎？
Listen to me, though Stop it. Stop, okay?
幫個忙，不要告訴麗莎這件事
Do yourself a favor, and do not tell Lisa about this
直到達成協議
until it's a done deal
現在，你知道我比那更聰明了，Marv
Now, you know I'm smarter than that, Marv
你會成為一名金融分析師嗎？
You're gonna be a financial analyst?
是的，我是
Yes, I am
我是，寶貝，它馬上就開始了
I am, babe, and it starts immediately
我和Marv談過了，他說他們真的可以用
I was talking to Marv, and he says that they could really use
在他的公司裡有我這樣的人
somebody with my skill set at his firm
太好了
That's great
這是一個很好的機會
That's a great opportunity
嗯...是啊，我是說，我
Um... yeah, I mean, I'm-I'm
我對此基本上很興奮，你知道嗎？
I'm basically pumped up about it, you know?
你很有彈性，寶貝
You are so resilient, baby Mmm
你不停地反彈，我為你感到驕傲
You keep bouncing back I am so proud of you
是
Yep
我愛你
I love you
我也愛你
I love you, too
媽，丁字褲當然會
Ma, of course the thong is gonna
在戰利品洞裡砍你
cut you in the booty hole
這就是它做的看，下次里昂
That's what it do Look, next time Leon
你告訴他，想給某人穿丁字褲
want to stick somebody in a thong, you tell him
他需要戴上它並得到一面鏡子
that he need to put it on and get a mirror
看看他的球做了什麼
and check and see what his balls do
我不在乎他是否是你的牧師
I don't care if he is your pastor
會眾知道他是那樣的怪胎嗎？
Do the congregation know he a freak like that?
堅持住，媽媽
Hold on, Mama
先生，我能幫你嗎？
Can I help you, sir?
嗯
Um
我忍不住偷聽了你的談話
I couldn't help but overhear your conversation
對不起？你有點大聲
Excuse me? You kind of loud
那就下車吧
Well, then get out of my car
我不在你的車裡，我很明顯在我的車裡
I'm not in your car I'm clearly in my car
不，你在我車裡，你說話聲音夠大的
No, you're in my car You're speaking loud enough
你是什麼，音量控制警察？
What are you, the volume control police?
我不確定這是否是一件事
I'm not sure if that's even a thing
別管閒事
Mind your business
你的生意正成為我的生意
Your business is becoming my business
你為什麼不在擋風玻璃上工作？
Why don't you work on your windshield?
現在你真的是我的生意
Now you're really in my business
可能看起來像萬花筒
Probably look like a kaleidoscope
當你仔細看的時候
when you look through it
你知道，你為什麼不乾脆...？
You know, why don't you just...?
你可能覺得自己像只小蜜蜂
You probably feel like a little honeybee
足夠一次看18件事，
Enough Looking at 18 things at one time,
但實際上你只是在看一件事
but really you're just looking at one thing
我...我...我現在就去做你的生意
I-I-I'm gonna get in your business now
告訴你媽媽，她可以去買一盒G弦
Tell your mother that she can go buy a box of G-strings
用她噁心的屁股
with her nasty ass
你現在在說我媽媽？
You're talking about my mama now?
任何牧師在他的球上穿丁字褲
Any pastor that's putting a thong on his balls
上帝是不對的
ain't right with God
噓。什麼？不要噓我
Pssh. What? Don't pssh me
嘶
Pssh
是
Yeah
我打賭那會傷到你的喉嚨
I bet that hurt your throat
開你的車
Drive your car
什麼，媽媽？
What, Mama?
你媽媽很討厭
Your mother's nasty
女孩，是啊，那是一隻被燒焦的小妖精
Girl, yeah, that's a little ol' burnt leprechaun
在我們的談話中，坐在我旁邊，看著這該死的燈
sitting next to me at this damn light all in our conversation
對不起？嘿，不，女孩，你知道他沒有金子
Excuse me? Hey Nah, girl, you know he ain't got no gold
你知道他沒有金子
You know he ain't got no gold
你長大了怎麼樣？再見，噓！
How about you grow up? Bye, boo!
嘿
Hey
說話...說到烤麵包，如果你...？
Speak... speaking of toast, if you...?
該死，泰迪
Goddamn it, Teddy
我要工作嘿，喲！
I gotta work Hey, yo!
你按誰的喇叭...？我們走吧！
Who you honk...? Let's go!
我甚至看不到我的鏡子在哪裡？
I can't even see Where's my mirror?
喲，夥計！嘿，你在按誰的喇叭？
Yo, man! Hey, who you honking at?
所以，再次對系統進行遊戲，
So, game the system again,
是嗎，泰迪？
did we, Teddy?
斯圖爾特，你有什麼問題嗎？
Stewart, what is your problem with me?
泰迪，我對你的問題是學生喜歡你
My problem with you, Teddy, is that students like you
降低這所高中的聲譽
bring down the reputation of this high school
你可能還有其他人
You may have everybody else
在這所學校被愚弄了，但我知道
at this school fooled, but I know
你實際上是在掩蓋事實
you're actually covering up for the fact
你真的沒那麼聰明
that you're really just not that smart
事實上，你可能是這所學校最笨的學生
In fact, you might be the dumbest student at this school
哦
Uh-oh
是啊
Yeah  -  Uh-oh
哦
Uh-oh
我是音樂老師
I am the music teacher
我對生物學教學一竅不通
I don't know the first thing about teaching biology
哦，看在上帝的份上！
Oh, for God's sakes!
沒有音樂節目的哪一部分
What part of there is no musical program
你不明白嗎，崔西？
do you not understand, Trish?
沒有人會進入常春籐盟校
Nobody's getting into Ivy League schools
靠巴松管獎學金哦，媽的
on a bassoon scholarship Oh, shit
你知道，我不聰明
You know, I'm not book smart
斯圖爾特比我聰明
Stewart's smarter than me
但是你知道我不是什麼嗎？
But you know what I'm not?
我不是天生的怪胎，斯圖
I'm not a freak of nature, Stew
哦，斯圖
Uh-oh, Stew
別這樣，泰迪
Don't do this, Teddy
嘿，快問大家
Hey, quick question, everybody
這裡有人見過斯圖爾特脫下襯衫嗎？
Has anybody here ever seen Stewart with his shirt off?
這是胎記這是胎記！
It's a birthmark It's a birthmark!
如果是胎記，讓我們現在就去看看，證明一下
If it's a birthmark, let us see it right now Prove it
你們都想看我的胎記嗎？
You all want to see my birthmark?
是的！來吧！我快死了！
Yes! Come on! I'm dying!
我會證明的。看到了嗎？
I'll prove it. See?
這是胎記！
It's a birthmark!
你胸口上有個豬屁股，夥計
You got a pig's butthole on your chest, man
裡面沒有洞，那怎麼可能是一個炮眼呢？
There's no hole in it, so how could it be a butthole?
你有第三個乳頭，夥計！
You got a third nipple, man!
誰是下一個，多洛雷斯？
Who's next, Dolores?
這個年輕人就在這裡
This young man right here
嘿。怎麼了，斯圖爾特？
Hey. What's up, Stewart?
我們過得很愉快，不是嗎？
We had good times, didn't we?
我笑我們笑得多厲害
I laugh at how much we laughed
那是一些
That's some
所以，呃
So, uh
你當校長多久了，夥計？
how long you been the principal, man?
持續兩年
Going on two years
哇，是啊。不容易，
Wow Yeah. Wasn't easy,
但是，呃，用我的大腦和球棒清理了這個地方
but, uh, cleaned this place up using my brain and my bat
與我們上高中的時候相反，
As opposed to when we went to high school,
現在，如果你有D平均數，你就出局了
now, if you have a D average, you're out
你能做到嗎？
Can you do that?
泰迪，我可以做任何我想做的事
I can do whatever I want, Teddy
這是我的房子
This my house
對不起，最後一部分是什麼？
I'm sorry, what what was that last part?
我說看看你周圍
I said look around you
這是...我的
This is... my
房子
house
對不起，我問一下，你的聲音是黑色的嗎？
Excuse me for asking, but are you doing a black voice?
不，不，不是黑色的聲音
No, no. Not a black voice
你確定？我聽不到顏色
You sure? I don't hear color
嗯，沃克先生，是什麼讓你回到皮埃蒙特？
Mmm What brings you back to Piedmont, Mr. Walker?
現在，我正在從一份令人驚歎的銷售工作轉變過來
Right now I'm transitioning from an amazing job in sales
金融領域的工作，唯一的
to a job in finance, and the only thing
這真的阻礙了這種轉變
that's really holding up this transition
我沒有GED嗎
is me not having my GED
所以，我不知道，我在想也許我可以
So, I don't know, I was thinking maybe I could
讓你穿過一些T，點一些我的
get you to cross some T's, dot some I's
也許你可以
Maybe you could do
對老朋友的恩惠
a favor for an old friend
有些事情永遠不會改變，嗯，泰迪？
Some things just never change, huh, Teddy?
你想讓我幫你嗎
You want me to help you
找到獲得文憑的捷徑
find a shortcut to getting your diploma
不
No
是
Yes
嗯
Hmm
我希望我能。我真的喜歡
I wish I could. I really do
但是你得走了
But you would have to go
去夜校學習如何通過GED考試，
to night school to learn how to pass the GED test,
不幸的是，我們這裡不提供夜校
and unfortunately we don't offer night school here
我很抱歉，泰迪
I'm so sorry, Teddy
讓我帶你出去
Let me walk you out
你想摸她嗎？
You want to touch her?
對不起？開始
I'm sorry? Come on
摸摸我的大黑球棒
Touch my big black bat
嗯，不，我是
Um, no, I'm
說吧，打招呼
Go ahead, say hi
啊！
Ah!
你以前叫我瘋狂斯圖爾特
You used to call me Crazy Stewart
現在你叫我蝙蝠俠
Now you call me Batman
去除安德烈的節拍，魯迪
Remove the Beats by Andre, Rudy
學校政策校園內不戴耳機
School policy no headphones on campus
除非你用的是羅塞塔石碑
unless you're using Rosetta Stone
嘿，呃...嘿，斯圖，你認為你在服用
Hey, uh... hey, Stew, you think you're taking
和這些孩子在一起的正確方法？
the right approach here with these kids?
他們看起來有點緊張，夥計
They look a little stressed out, man
我正在為現實世界做準備，泰迪，好嗎？
I am preparing them for the real world, Teddy, okay?
我可能不是他們最好的朋友，
I may not be their best friend,
但是這裡的每個人都尊重我好嗎
but everyone here respects me Okay
什麼他媽的，斯圖爾特？嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿
What the fuck, Stewart? Uh, hey, hey, hey, hey
卡特小姐，我們來看一下語言
Let's watch the language, please, Miss Carter
為什麼你要把AP演算添加到我的課程負荷中，
Why did you add AP Calculus to my class load,
知道我已經有了
knowing good and well I already have
五個單元教加夜校？
five units to teach plus night school?
太多了等等，等等
It's too much Wait, hold on
你是...你是夜校老師？
You're... you're the night school teacher?
不，我只是個喜歡穿女衫的婊子
No, I'm just a bitch that like to wear blouses
是的，我是夜校老師
Yes, I'm the night school teacher
小妖精，你給我帶了些干三葉草嗎？
Did you bring me some dried shamrocks, leprechaun?
這還不好笑
It's still not funny
等等，等等，等等
Wait, well, hold up
斯圖，你為什麼告訴我你
Stew, why'd you just tell me that you
這裡沒有夜校嗎？
don't have night school here?
你為什麼這麼說？
Why would you say that?
我這麼說是因為泰迪和我一起上學
I said that because Teddy and I went to school together
坦率地說，他是一個糟糕的學生，
He is, quite frankly, a terrible student,
我不希望這個元素出現在這裡
and I did not want that element in here
我不在乎他是否像Minion一樣愚蠢
I don't care if he's as dumb as a Minion
如果他願意，歡迎他來上我的課
He is welcome to take my class if he wants
謝謝你。謝謝你
Thank you. Thank you for that
不客氣，因為你需要它
You're welcome Cause you-you need it
凱莉，我們能記下真相嗎？
Carrie, can we just take down the 'tude?
恩？真的嗎？
'Tude? Really?
不，我是
No, I'm
你甚至沒有看到這種態度的開始
You haven't even seen the beginning of this attitude
哦，我——我等著，再對我說一遍
Oh, I-I Wait, say that to me again
我道歉
I apologize
這是一個糟糕的詞語選擇
That was a poor choice of words
我只是說我需要你向我表示敬意
I just mean I need you to show me the respect
你會向你的老闆展示
that you would show your boss
因為這是你的房子，對吧？
Because this is your house, right?
哦，你...你和他一起做了黑色的聲音？
Oh, you... you did the black voice thing with him?
這不是一個黑色的聲音
It's not a black voice
實際上，沒有一個黑色的聲音
In actuality, not a black voice
不，你的聲音很黑
No, you do a black voice
你不記得你在開會的時候，
You don't remember when you was in that meeting,
你想，我們會在這裡把它點燃
you was like, We gonna get it lit up in here
會議開始了！
This meeting lit!
天很亮
It was very lit
你是在員工會議上做的
You did it at the staff meeting
當你喜歡的時候，我會保留一百英鎊。
when you were like, I keep it one hundred.
我什麼時候沒把它保存一百年？
When have I never kept it one hunnid?
當你把AP演算添加到我的類負載中時
When you added that AP Calculus to my class load
好吧，同意不同意聽著，我討厭分手
All right, agree to disagree Listen, I hate to break up
這種妄想的快樂一方，
this pleasure party of delusion,
但是我還有工作要做
but I have work to do
哇，那麼，請原諒
Wow So, if you'll excuse me
我- -我要盡我的努力
I'm-a do my thang
那是...那是一個黑色的聲音
That's... that's a black voice
看看活著的人！
Look alive, people!
讓我們有目的地行動吧！走，走，走，走，走！
Let's move with purpose! Go, go, go, go, go!
嘿。嘿，不要在我的大廳裡閒逛！
Hey. Hey No loitering in my hall!
能...他真能做到嗎？他能阻止我去這裡嗎？
Can... can he really do that? Can he keep me from going here?
不，他不能。事實上，這是一本教科書
No, he can't. As a matter of fact, here's a textbook
事實上，我現在就要開始上課
I'm actually going to set up the class right now
這學期的第一節課
for our first session of the semester
我們7點開始
We start at 7:00
是的，但是這本書有點厚
Yeah, but this-this book is just kind of thick
我想這更像是一張傳單
I thought it would be more like a leaflet
你以為你可以補習四年高中
You thought you could cram four years of high school
變成傳單？
into a leaflet?
不，也許你是
No Maybe you are
正如斯圖爾特所說的那樣愚蠢等等，不，不，不，不，不
as dumb as Stewart says Wait, wait, no, no, no, no
不，不，我沒想到
No, no, I didn't I didn't think that
去圖書館，然後我就
Go to the library, then I just
我會抓住小瘦骨嶙峋的侏儒！
I'll hold on Little scrawny midget!
我會堅持下去
I'll hold on to it
嗯，嗯，我被絆倒了
Mm-hmm I'm trippin
我在沿著交通學校的路線思考
I'm thinking along the lines of traffic school
聽著，來不來對我沒什麼影響
Look, come or not makes me no difference
我不按人頭付費
I don't get paid by the head
或者你可以找到夜校
Or maybe you can find a night school
這確實是傳單上的內容
that does teach from a leaflet
你知道一件事...？
You-you know of one that...?
不，不，不，不，我會保留它
No, no, no I'm-I'm gonna keep it
有一個好的
Have a good one
marv，我不知道這件GED的事
Marv, I do not know about this GED thing
我沒有，夥計。老師很嚴厲
I don't, man The teacher is tough as hell
抓住馬伕，讓我回擊你
Hold on Marv, let me hit you back
喲！
Yo!
哦，媽的！
Oh, shit!
撐住！停下，停下！
Hold up! Stop, stop!
你在做什麼？我在做什麼？
What you doing? What's it look like I'm doing?
呃，看起來你拖著我的車
Uh, it look like you towing my car
我把車停在殘疾人區了嗎？
Did I park in a handicap spot?
你錯過了那輛車的最後四筆付款
You've missed the last four payments on that car
它被收回了
It's getting repossessed
你要帶著我的孩子坐我的車嗎？
You gonna take my car with my baby in the back?
沒看到裡面有該死的嬰兒
Don't see no goddamn baby in there
嬰兒就在那裡
The baby right there
你沒聽到嗎？我不這麼認為
You don't hear that? I don't think so
嘿，夥計，我說過不要這麼做
Hey, man, I said don't do it
我不玩了
I'm not playing
讓開，夥計
Get out of the way, dude
停下，夥計
Stop, man
我的孩子在這裡！
I got my baby in here!
車要開了
The car is leaving
讓開，夥計，我帶你離開
Get out of the way, dude I'll show you leaving
來吧，夥計，我有東西給你
Come on, man I've got something for your ass
下車
Get out of the car
你想玩那個遊戲嗎？是啊！
You want to play that game? Yeah!
你想看什麼嗎？那麼，來吧！
You want to see something? Come on, then!
再見
Bye
笨蛋
Dumb-ass
哦，上帝！
Oh, God!
很高興你們都喜歡這個節目
Glad y'all enjoyed the show
告訴我未婚妻我又出車禍了！
Tell my fiancee I got in another accident!
呃
Uh
凱莉，對吧？哦
Carrie, right? Oh
所以，儘管我們有教科書大小的教科書，
So, even though we got textbook-sized textbooks,
你決定加入我們
you decided to join us
好吧，坐吧
Well, grab a seat
我們幾分鐘後開始
We'll get started in a few
呃，好吧，在我現在這麼做之前，我知道我們下車了
Uh, okay, before I do that now, I know we got off
走錯了路，所以我在想
on the wrong foot, so I was thinking
我不知道...我不知道你有沒有時間吃飯，
I don't know... I don't know if you had time for dinner or not,
所以我自己承擔了
so I took it upon myself
去給你買一個我個人最喜歡的
to go and get you one of my personal favorites
這是A區最好的墨西哥人
It's the best Mexican here in the A
哦。謝謝你
Oh. Thank you
你想得真周到，泰迪
That is so thoughtful of you, Teddy
看看這個
So, check this out
我翻看了你高中時的一些舊記錄
I went through some of your old high school records
嗯嗯數學，
Uh-huh Math,
科學，英語，你是個糟糕的學生
science, English you was a horrible student
那你怎麼了？
What was going on with you then?
你被虐待了嗎？
Was you being abused or something?
凱莉，我的事
Carrie, the thing with me
我更喜歡用這個世界作為我的教室
is I prefer to use the world as my classroom
老實說，我不是
And to be honest with you, I'm not a
我不像其他人
I'm not like the rest of these folks
我不是你所說的夜校學生
I'm just not what you would call a night school person
所以我想，也許你和我可以互相照顧
So I figure, maybe you and I can look out for one another
你幫我，我幫你
You help me, I help you
你支持我，我支持你
You got my back, I got your back
不管怎樣，但這只是一次談話
Whatever, but it's just a conversation
享受你的玉米餅吧
So enjoy your tacos
那微笑能照亮一個房間，不是嗎？
That smile can light up a room, can't it?
我不去那裡
I ain't going there
記得我嗎，彭德喬？
Remember me, pendejo?
如果不是Pubey McGee
Well, if it isn't Pubey McGee
奶酪蛋糕酒吧在這裡，嗯？
The cheesecake puber is here, huh?
見到我很驚訝，兄弟？
Surprised to see me, bro?
考慮到你解雇了我，你不應該這麼做
You shouldn't be, considering that you got me fired
我沒有讓你被解雇是的，你被解雇了
I did not get you fired Yes, you did
我在客服部門工作
I worked in customer service
很久以來，每個人都知道這一點
for a long time Everybody knows that
顧客總是對的
the customer is always right
小費是我的生計，我有20英鎊給你
Tips are my livelihood I had a 20 coming your way
賬單是800美元
The bill was $800
我有一筆60美元的錢，夥計
I had a buck sixty coming to me, man
好吧。那是你的錯好吧，我們開始吧
Okay. That's your fault Okay, let's begin
這裡誰喜歡墨西哥玉米卷？
Who here likes tacos?
哦！哦，哦，哦！
Oh! Oh, oh Ooh!
他們吃素？
They vegetarian?
因為除非是烤肉，否則我不吃肉
Cause I don't eat meat unless it's barbecue
讓我們看看泰迪給我們帶來了什麼
Let's see what Teddy brought us
呃，我們有卡爾·阿薩達
Uh, we got carne asada
這邊請
There you go
有，呃，艾爾牧師
There's, uh, al pastor
哦，謝謝你...你喜歡嗎？嗯
Oh, thanks You... you like that? Um
卡妮塔？你喜歡carnitas嗎？
Carnitas? You like carnitas?
給你，女孩哦！
There you go, girl Ooh!
呃...呃，對不起，嘿！
Uh... uh, excuse me Hey!
凱莉，我真的有那些墨西哥玉米卷給你吃
Carrie, I-I had actually got those tacos for you to eat
我知道
I know
看，同學們，泰迪去了
See, class, Teddy went to
仙人掌屋試圖說服我
Cactus House to try to win me over
但這是交易，泰迪
But here's the deal, Teddy
如果你想親我的屁股，
If you're trying to kiss my ass,
你得比那好一點
you're gonna have to come a little bit better than that
我說的是蒸龍蝦
I'm talking, like, steamed lobster
在通心粉和奶酪裡，
inside a macaroni and cheese,
帶著布羅克裡尼的一面
with a side of broccolini
你知道我在說什麼嗎？一些奇特的東西
You know what I'm saying? Something fancy
不是沒有我可以去的快餐店
Not no fast food place where I could
用我自己的零亂的薪水去買這個
go buy this with my own little raggedy paycheck
嗯，實際上有一個
Well, there's actually a
實際上有一種特殊的鱷梨色拉醬
there's actually a special guacamole
如果你想在我的班上取得成功，
If you want to succeed in my class,
你需要做這項工作
you need to do the work
就這麼簡單
It's just that simple
是嗎？呃，快速提問
Yes? Uh, quick question
嗯，那麼蒸龍蝦怎麼樣？
Uh, so yes on the steamed lobster?
不，先生
No, sir
這就是我喜歡稱之為可教的時刻。
That's what I like to call a teachable moment.
好吧，所以沒有龍蝦
Okay, so no lobster
嗯，好吧，讓我們開始做一些介紹
Um, all right, let's go ahead and do some introductions
我會開始
I'll start
我叫凱莉
My name is Carrie
白天，我教書
During the day, I teach
課程太多，錢太少
way too many classes for way too little money
所以我來這裡是想多賺點錢
So I'm here to try to make a little extra cash
所以我能負擔得起房租和抗生素等奢侈品
so I can afford such luxuries as rent and antibiotics
因為這份工作有時讓我生病
Cause this job makes me sick sometimes
呃，你是下一個
Uh, you're next
是的，你
Yes, you
薩拉姆·阿拉庫姆
As-salaam alaikum
怎麼了？
What up, though?
傑倫是這個名字
Jaylen's the name
我已經工作了14年了
I've been working for the last 14 years
在麥克阿瑟裝瓶廠
at the MacArthur Bottling Plant
被機器人取代了
and just got replaced by a robot
還有我的肋骨，我的克婁巴特拉，
And my rib, my Cleopatra,
我的王后，我的賤女人，
my queen, my bottom bitch,
我14年的妻子，她就像，喲，
my wife of 14 years, she was like, Yo,
如果你想要選擇，你必須拿到你的GED
if you want options, you gonna have to get your GED
要麼就是這樣，要麼就是打掃房間
It's either that or end up cleaning rooms
在貝斯特韋斯特酒店，工資減半。
at the Best Western for half your salary.
如果你認識傑伊，那是行不通的
And if you know Jay, that ain't gonna work
嘿，讓我這麼說吧，
Hey, let me let me just say this,
好吧，當我登上講台的時候
okay, while I got the platform
對我來說，我第一次醒來時看到終結者，
For me, I first got woke when I seen Terminator,
我意識到這不僅僅是一部電影；
and I realized it wasn't just a movie;
這是預言
it was prophecy
首先由3.5 %的人識別，
First identified by the 3.5-Percenters,
但那是另一次對話
but that's another conversation
我們就這樣說吧
Let's just put it like this
革命不會自動化
The revolution will not be roboticized
嗯
Mm-hmm
不是傑伊的手錶
Not on Jay's watch
嗯？
Huh?
真正的黑鬼
Real nigga shit
嗯？謝謝你，傑倫
Huh? Thank you, Jaylen
我會確保不帶我的Roomba
I'll make sure I don't bring my Roomba
下一節課
to the next class
我妻子上倫巴課
My wife takes rumba classes
我不明白，讓我們繼續前進
I don't get it Let's keep it moving
呃，你呢，女士？
Uh, how about you, ma'am?
是啊
Yeah Oh
好吧。嗨，夥計們
Okay. Hi, gang
我叫特裡薩，
My name is Theresa,
我高中就輟學了
and I dropped out of high school
當我懷上第一個孩子的時候
when I was pregnant with my first child
我現在的丈夫蘭迪，
My now-husband, Randy,
他把我撞倒後，我們結婚了
well, we got married after he knocked me up
然後我們又有了兩個孩子，所以我們有了
Then we had two more kids, so we have
現在有三個小流氓，很有趣
three little rascals now, and it's fun
我們只是在水下
We're just a little underwater
現在，所以我想拿到GED，希望如此
right now, so I wanted to get my GED and hopefully
在太晚之前加入勞動力隊伍
enter the workforce before it's too late
我們必須住在蘭迪父母的洗衣房裡
and we have to live in Randy's parents' laundry room
我很幸運
I'm blessed
真幸運
So blessed
上帝是好的
God is good
這是怎麼回事
That's what's up
呃，你呢，小姐？
Uh, how about you, young lady?
哦
Oh
嘿，呃，怎麼了？我是米拉
Hey, uh, what's up? I'm Mila
我被高中開除了
I got kicked out of my high school
因為他們在我的儲物櫃裡發現了莫莉
because they found some Molly in my locker
嗯，我可以避免未成年人
Mm-hmm And I can avoid juvie
如果我拿到了GED，那麼我就在這裡
if I get my GED, so here I am
我太激動了，酷
I'm so psyched Cool
看看你，都很可愛，讓美國再次變得偉大
Look at you, all cute, making America great again
母狗
Bitch
那麼，你的故事是什麼，夥計們？
So, what's your story, guy?
嗯，我叫路易斯·弗洛雷斯
Um, my name is Luis Flores
我有一份很好的服務員工作
I had a great job as a waiter
小費很多
Lot of money in tips
直到我被無故解雇
Until I was fired without cause
一點理由都沒有
No reason at all
fire的過去式和過去分詞
Fired
我不知道為什麼我不知道
I don't know why I have no idea
他為什麼看著我，我不知道
why he's looking at me I don't
很好
It's fine
這只是時間到了的信號
It's just a sign that it's time
讓我做一些不同的事情
for me to do something different
你看，我來到這個國家
You see, I came to this country
從墨西哥來實現我的夢想
from Mexico to fulfill my dream
成為一名歌手作家
of being a singersongwriter
哦，像胡裡奧·伊格萊西亞斯？
Oh, like Julio Iglesias?
不，不像胡裡奧·伊格萊西亞斯
No, not like Julio Iglesias
他很差勁
He sucks
更像賈斯汀比伯
More like Justin Bieber
或者賈斯汀·汀布萊克或者T -疼痛
or Justin Timberlake or T-Pain
等等，等等，等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait
你現在是不是有點老了，像是成為一名流行歌星了？
Aren't you a little old to, like, be a pop star now?
你不是有點年輕就要死了嗎？
Aren't you a little young to die?
這是怎麼回事
That's what's up
但是現在我要成為一名牙科醫生。
But now I'm going to become a dental hy-enist.
因為我的牙齒很棒
Cause I have great teeth
所以我想我會是個天生的
So I think I'd be a natural
什麼？
A what?
牙科醫生
Dental hy-enist
也許你應該看看
Maybe you should see one
因為，你們知道嗎，很臭，夥計們
Cause, you know what, pretty stinky, guys
好吧。大家好
All right. Hey, everybody
我是麥肯齊
I'm Mackenzie
呃，他們叫我巨無霸
Uh, they call me Big Mac
哦，我們喜歡麥當勞
Oh, we love McDonald's
什麼？
What?
麥當勞？
McDonald's?
對不起，什麼？
I'm sorry, what?
漢堡店的米奇·D店
From the burger joint, Mickey D's
羅納德·麥當勞
Ronald McDonald's
兩個全牛肉餡餅，
Two all-beef patties,
特殊調味汁、萵苣、奶酪，
special sauce, lettuce, cheese,
在芝麻麵包上。嗯
on a sesame-seed bun. Hmm
沒聽說過嗎？
Never heard of it?
哦，這將是一個漫長的學期
Ooh, it's gonna be a long semester
好吧，不管怎樣，
Go on Well, anyway,
呃，我的膝蓋和背部都被抬高了
uh, my knees and my back are really jacked up
從在何曼搬家公司工作30年，
from working at He-Man Movers for 30 years,
所以我決定拿我的GED，這樣我就可以升職了
so I decided to get my GED so that I could move up
到管理崗位，下車
to a management position, get off the truck
我兒子我們叫他小麥克
And my son we call him Little Mac
他決定退學
he has decided to drop out of school
所以我和他做了一筆交易:我拿到了GED，
So I made a deal with him: I get my GED,
他拿到了文憑
he gets his diploma
小逆轉心理學
Little reverse psychology
好
All right
你叫什麼名字？
And what's your name?
嘿，喲，怎麼了？我是鮑比
Hey, yo, what up? I'm Bobby
這就是我所說的
That's what that's what I'm talking about
那是光明會，我就是這麼說的
That's Illuminati That's what I'm saying
看，這裡的黑鬼，但他不在這裡
See, the nigga here, but he ain't here
就像他們在看你一樣，
It's like they watching you,
你認為你在看他們嗎
and you think you watching them
他們就是這麼做的
That's what they do
所以你有鮑比·數字
So you got Bobby Digital
他在這裡，但他不在
He here, but he not
那是圖帕克·科切拉
That's Tupac Coachella
你知道我在說什麼嗎？
You know what I'm saying?
他在...你看到了嗎？
And he in the... You see?
你們都不知道...？好吧，嗯
Y'all don't...? All right, um
那可能不是真正的黑鬼。嘿
That probably ain't even a real nigga. Hey
你瘋了嗎？這是- -這是Skype
Are you on crack? It's-it's Skype
唷，孩子，很難被吵醒
Whew, boy, it's hard to be woke
很難被吵醒
It's hard to be woke
什麼醒了？
What is woke?
好吧，歡迎大家
Okay, well, welcome, everyone
真的很好。我們都見過面
Really nice. We've all met
嗯，我們沒有，呃
Well, we didn't, uh
我們沒有遇見我們沒有遇見每個人
we didn't meet we didn't meet everyone
我沒有，呃泰迪，呃，早些時候，
I didn't, uh Teddy, uh, earlier,
你說過，不像這些人，
you said, unlike these folks,
你不是夜校類型的人，
you're not a night school type of person,
所以我認為你不在乎
so I didn't think you cared
對嗎？
Is that right?
你沒有
Well, you didn't
你沒聽清楚，因為我絕不會這麼說
you didn't hear it right, cause I would never say that
關於我不認識的人
about people that I don't know
你知道嗎？這是一個完美的分段
You know what? This is a perfect segue
我會跟著你，我會站起來
I'll just follow your lead, and I'll stand up
我是泰迪·沃克
I am Teddy Walker
嗯，關於我的一個有趣的事實:我真的去了這裡
Uh, a little fun fact about me: I actually went here
哦，我也剛訂婚
Oh I'm also newly engaged
他的未婚妻退出了他的聯盟
His fiancee is out of his league
對不起，什麼？
I'm sorry, what?
沒什麼。你做得很好
Nothing. You're doing great
我說，繼續
I said, Keep going
每個人都愛你。
Everybody loves you.
你未婚妻感覺怎麼樣
How does your fiancee feel about
你在夜校嗎？
you being in night school?
哦，她很好
Oh, she good
她喜歡
She loves it
他沒告訴她什麼
He ain't told her shit
她喜歡
She loves it
我注意到你的聲音
I noticed that your voice
就提高了整整一個八度
just went up a whole octave
現在，從我在研究生院的心理學研究來看，
Now, from my studies of psychology in grad school,
我知道那意味著你在胡說八道
I know that that means that you're bullshitting
我沒有胡說八道
Ain't no bullshit in me
我告訴你如果你和她撒謊，
I tell you what if you're lying with her,
不要騙她，但我不騙她...我不說謊
don't lie to her But I don't... I don't lie
聽起來像是胡說八道
Sound like some bullshit to me
每個人都看穿了你
Everyone sees right through you
好吧，我們怎麼樣...？嗯
Okay, how about we...? Mm-hmm
如果我們遵循你關於聲音的理論
If we go by your theory about the voice thing
我認為我們是我認為我們都是
I think that we're I think that we're all
偏離軌道
getting off track
這小子肯定在撒謊
This boy definitely lying
我不是你不能勝過大自然母親
I am not You can't outsmart Mother Nature
這就是女人
And that's what that-that's what a woman is
哥哥，尤其是黑人婦女
Brother Especially a black woman
你知道，這是多麼正確
You know, how That's correct
女孩很聰明，夥計，該死的
Girls are smart, dude Goddamn it
就像，真的，該死的
Like, literally, damn it
即使他沒有告訴她，那又怎樣？
Even if he didn't tell her, so what?
好吧，這是我告訴Randy的事情
Okay, here's the thing I told Randy
他是第一個和我上床的人...不是真的
that he was the first guy I slept with... not true
嘿，我想自我介紹，但我不能
Hey, I'm trying to introduce myself, and I can't
你不尊重你的女王，因為如果你尊重了，
You don't respect your queen, cause if you did,
那個婊子會知道你在哪裡好嗎
that bitch would know where you at Okay
泰迪
Teddy
不要對你的女王撒謊
Don't lie to your queen
好吧，夥計們，如果你們要逃跑
Okay, guys If you're busting off
在她那樣的內臟裡，她可能帶著你的種子
in her guts like that, she might be carrying your seed
我喜歡這個對話
I feel like this conversation
所以你不只是在騙她；你對你的孩子撒謊
So you ain't just lying to her; you lying to your child
媽的！如果是你的屁股婊子，
Shit! If it's your bottom bitch,
她知道你很蠢，媽媽
she know you stupid, fam
我說的一切，fam，看-看，算了吧
All I'm saying, fam, look-look Forget it
好吧，你未婚妻怎麼不知道你在哪裡？
Okay How your fiancee don't know where you at?
天黑了
It's after dark
這不是萬聖節，媽媽
This ain't Halloween, fam
我完了
I'm done
我姐姐知道我在哪裡，好嗎？
My sister know where I'm at, okay?
她一直住在阿肯色州
And she live all the way in Arkansas
好吧。這是交易，同學們
Okay. Here's the deal, class
你每天晚上都會有家庭作業
You will be given homework every night
就像普通高中一樣
just like regular high school
那麼
And now
突擊測驗
a pop quiz
這樣我就能更好地瞭解你們都在哪裡
just so I can get a better idea of where you all are
等等。第一天我們有考試？
Wait, wait. We got a we got a test on the first day?
泰迪，這是一個突擊測驗，好嗎？
Teddy, it's a pop quiz, okay?
看這裡，夥計們
Look here, folks
如果你來這裡學習，我是來教書的
I am here to teach if you're here to learn
否則，你現在就可以離開我的班級
Otherwise, you can get out of my class right now
這是怎麼回事
That's what's up
歡迎來到夜校
Welcome to night school
這邊請
There you go
太可怕了，夥計，太可怕了！
It was terrible, man Terrible!
她不像老師
Like, she's not like the teachers
我們在那一天
that we had back in the day
什麼？這個女人是一堵磚牆，
What? This woman is a brick wall,
我不能，我不能和她一起工作
and I can't I can't work her
我不能做磚牆
I can't work a brick wall
你在做什麼？
What are you what are you doing?
我正在努力減肥
I'm working out I'm trying to shed some LBs
我想感覺健康，為什麼我還要問？
I want to feel fit Uh, why am I even asking?
同時，請停止支付一切費用，
In the meantime, please stop paying for everything,
你必須找份臨時工作
and you have to get a temp job
你不認為我一直在找工作嗎？
You don't think I've been looking for a job?
你瘋了嗎？我在跑步機上
What are you, crazy? I'm on a treadmill
我想要的工作，不是
The jobs that I want, they are not
會給一個高中輟學生
going to give to a high school dropout
你不能一直對麗莎撒謊
Well, you can't keep lying to Lisa
好嗎？你知道嗎，我要走了
Okay? You know what, I'm gonna go
現在在Monster.com，看看有沒有新的東西出現
on Monster.com right now, see if anything new popped up
你要去哪裡？你要找到什麼
What are you going what are you going to find
在Monster.com？哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
on Monster.com? Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
好了，我們要找銷售助理
Okay, here we go Sales associate wanted
營銷技巧是必須的。
Marketing skills a must.
和...等待它
And... wait for it
不需要GED。
No GED required.
你必須跳下去，夥計，這太棒了
You gotta jump on this, man This is perfect
這是上帝的雞肉
It's chicken from the Lord
所以他...所以他成功了？
So he... so he made it?
是的，先生，他做到了
Yes, sir, he did
是
Yeah
我可以我可以用這個
I-I can I can work with this
你可以嗎？是
You can? Yeah
基本上，你想做什麼
Basically, what you want to do
你想...你想提升顧客的品味
you want to... you want to uplift your customers' palate
是的，先生，當他們咬的時候
Yes, sir When they bite
在你的食物中，你想要他們的味蕾
into your food, you want their taste buds
大聲尖叫，哈利路亞！
to scream out, Hallelujah!
宣講吧，泰迪兄弟
Preach it, Brother Teddy
你真是天賜良機
You are a godsend
我是推銷員，夥計
I'm a salesman, man
我就是這麼做的，好嗎？
That's what I do, okay?
現在，談到頭銜，我甚至不在乎
Now, when it comes to titles, I don't even care
營銷總監由你決定
Marketing director that's up to you
WWJD，在這一點上，耶穌會怎麼做？
WWJD, at this point What would Jesus do?
是的，先生，我問的一件事
Yes, sir The one thing that I ask
對你來說，時間是靈活的，
is for you to be flexible with the hours,
因為我要拿到我的GED
cause I'm getting my GED
泰迪哥哥，你正在進步
You are bettering yourself, Brother Teddy
是的，這就是做一名基督徒的意義所在
Yeah That's what being a Christian is all about
是的，修正了這一點
Yeah, amen to that
阿門
Amen
是啊，光榮是
Yeah Glory be
這應該非常適合你
This should fit you perfectly
泰迪哥哥，
Brother Teddy,
我一直在等待上帝
I have been waiting on the Lord
給我帶來一個像你這樣的小個子男人
to bring me a pint-sized little man like you
填完這個，給你
to fill this out, and here you are
我不會這麼做的
I'm-I'm not gonna do that
艾薩克兄弟，我——我是個黑人
Brother Isaac, I-I'm a black man
2018年我不能穿上雞服
I can't put on a chicken suit in 2018
站在公路邊上
and stand on the side of a highway
不賣該死的雞
and hawk no goddamn chicken
現在，如果營銷職位不是你想要的
Now, if the marketing position isn't what you
我們可以想像
had in mind, we can figure
這是怎麼回事？
What is going on?
你知道嗎？我們得在裡面插個別針
You know what? We're gonna have to put a pin in that
那是消防演習嗎？好了，各位
Is that a fire drill? All right, everybody
讓我們聚在一起，時間到了
Let's gather round The hour is upon us
最近的出口在哪？
Where's the closest exit?
是時候祈禱了是時候做什麼了？
It is time to pray It's time to what?
是時候祈禱了
It's time to pray Gather round
該死的。你的交易是什麼？
Goddamn. What is your deal?
什麼...？嘿，親愛的主夫人:我們感謝你
What's...? Hey, lady Dear Lord: We thank you
把小泰迪帶給我們
for bringing little Teddy to us
今天早上在這裡是的，先生
here this morning Yes, sir
這個小山雀
This little chickadee
嗯？
Huh?
與世界分享你珍貴的家禽
about your precious poultry with the world
我不會做的是在裡面做
What I'm not gonna do is do it in
夫人，夫人
Ma'am, ma'am
強壯的手！
Strong hands!
對不起！
Excuse me!
我不打算在小雞身上做...討厭的
What I'm not gonna do is do it in the chick... Goddamn
泰迪哥哥
Brother Teddy
他在你身上
He's in you
他在你心裡，不是嗎？
He's in you, ain't he?
雞肉套裝與否，
Chicken suit or not,
我們現在都在一起祈禱
we are all praying together right now
你今天會在這裡找到你的窩
that you're gonna find your nest here with us today
好，阿門，阿門
Okay Amen and amen
阿門！
Amen!
阿門。是的，先生！
Amen. Yes, sir!
歡迎，泰迪兄弟
Welcome, Brother Teddy
好了，各位，這是一個重要的日子
All right, everybody, this is a big day
嘿，兄弟，讓我很快地對你大喊大叫
Hey, brother, let me holler at you real quick
你們都在沉沒的地方嗎？
Are y'all in the Sunken Place?
讓我們通過食物分享耶穌。我們走吧
Let's share Jesus through our food. Let's go
午餐高峰來了
The lunch rush is upon us
什麼...午餐高峰？
What... lunch rush?
現在是上午10點
It's 10:00 a.m
我不明白
I don't understand
這怎麼會被認為是午餐高峰
how that could be considered a lunch rush
相信我，泰迪哥哥
Trust me, Brother Teddy
好吧，如果有...如果- -如果有什麼辦法我可以直接說
Okay, if there... if-if there's any way that I can just talk
女士們，早上好
to you about the Good morning, ladies
你好肉桂
Hello, Cinnamon
蘿茜
Roxy
女士們，你們好
Hello, ladies
圖蒂，換班怎麼樣？
Tootie, how was the shift?
好萊塢，你好嗎？
Hollywood, how you doing?
很高興見到你，利
Good to see you, Leigh
你好，維羅妮卡，你的輪班怎麼樣？
Hello, Veronica, how was your shift?
蘿茜，很高興見到你
Roxy, good to see you
現在，從你第一個晚上的家庭作業開始，
Now, from your first night of homework,
你們都應該非常熟悉畢達哥拉斯定理
you all should be very familiar with the Pythagorean theorem
好嗎？跟我說
All right? Say it with me
畢達哥拉斯學派...
Pythagorean...
畢達哥拉斯學派。
Pythagorean.
Pathegorinean。
Pathygorinean.
定理。定理。
Theorem. Theorem.
定理。你就是這麼說的
Theorem. That's how you say it
就是這樣
That's what it is
嘿，喲，鮑比，小心，媽媽！
Hey, yo, Bobby, watch out, fam!
我的天啊！
My God Oh!
什麼？！呵
What?! Ooh
哦！
Oh!
欺騙
Shit
你沒看到我在努力學習嗎？
Can't you see I'm trying to learn?
應該有人報警
Someone ought to call the cops
發生什麼事了？拿著！
What's happening? Take that!
哦！耶穌
Ooh! Jesus
放開我！放開我！
Get off me! Get off me!
他起床了，他起床了，他起床了
He's getting up, he's getting up, he's getting up
小心，媽媽！在你身後，黑鬼！
Watch out, fam! Behind you, nigga!
哦，我的天啊！
Oh, my God Oh!
哦，他剛剛踢了他一腳
Oh, he just kicked him in the
哦，我的上帝！哦！
Oh, my God! Oh!
哦！夠了！是啊！是啊！
Oh! Enough! Yeah! Yeah!
幹掉他！踩他的頭！
Finish him! Step on his head!
過來。打破它來吧！
Come here. Break it up Come on!
起來！
Up!
嘿，來吧！哦，嘿，夥計！
Hey, come on! Oh, hey, man!
我什麼都沒做
I didn't do shit
就在那裡
That's the stuff right there
讓我想起了過去
Reminds me of the old days
他們找錯人了
They had the wrong guy
請繼續你確定你很酷，
Please continue You sure you cool,
還是我們需要冷靜下來
or do we need to just chill
等著你做一個新的刀柄？
and wait for you to make a new shank?
請繼續畢達哥拉斯學派
Please continue with the Pythagorean
理論。
theory-em.
好吧
O-Okay
你知道我們應該為鮑比做什麼嗎？
You know what we ought to do for Bobby?
我們應該給他弄些煙，
We should get him, like, some smokes,
因為這些東西就像監獄裡的貨幣
cause that stuff is like currency in prison
那個和屁股
That and ass
好了，我們開始吧
Okay, here we go
這就是我們所說的直角三角形
So, this is what we call a right triangle
我們已經知道了三角形兩邊的值
And we already know the value of two sides of the triangle
哦，這對我們來說應該很容易
Oh That should make it very easy for us
計算斜邊
to calculate the hypotenuse Mmm, mmm
A平方加B平方等於C平方
A-squared plus B-squared equals C-squared
跟我說，夥計們
Say that with me, guys
A平方加B平方
A-squared plus B-squared
等於C平方
equals C-squared
非常好。泰迪？
Very good. Uh, Teddy?
你似乎從中得到了真正的樂趣
You seem to be getting a real kick out of this
她抓住你了，泰迪！
She got you, Teddy!
你想上來解決這個問題嗎？
You want to come up and solve the problem?
被逮捕了！
Busted!
如果，呃，那就是你
If, uh, that's what you
如果那是你想要我做的
if that's what you want me to do
上來
Come on up
來吧，泰迪，這個給你
Come on, Teddy You got this
你拿到了，泰迪·泰迪！
You got this, Teddy Teddy!
泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Teddy!
泰迪！泰德，泰迪，泰迪！
Teddy! Ted, Teddy, Teddy!
找到C的值
Find the value of C
你知道嗎？
You know what?
我想這裡面有些東西
I think there's something in here
喲，喲，喲！怎麼了，我的夜校？
Yo, yo, yo! What up, my night school?
你在找誰，fam？
Who you looking for, fam?
我是這所高中的校長，
I'm the principal of this high school,
我只是順道來看看
and I'm just dropping by to check on
他在這裡幹什麼？
What is he doing here?
和其他人一樣，我正在學習獲得GED
I'm studying to get my GED, like everybody else
所以，如果你不介意，我想重新學習
So, if you don't mind, I'd like to get back to learning
當然可以
Of course
抱歉打斷你
My apologies for interrupting
謝謝你
Thank you
事實上，我想觀察一下
Actually, I would like to observe
一分鐘，如果可以的話
for a minute, if that's okay
請繼續解決這個問題
Please, continue solving the problem
忘記我在這裡
Forget I'm here
涼爽的
Cool
我不介意
That's fine with me
好吧，如果我要這麼做，
Okay, so if I'm gonna do this,
讓我們一步一步地做，讓我們確保我們做得正確
let's do it step by step Let's make sure we do it right
首先，讓我們擺脫這條線
First things first let's get rid of this line
因為它寫得很潦草
Because it's written sloppy
讓我們把那個嬰兒抱進去
So let's get that baby in there Eight
對吧？
Right?
嗯，我們有這三個方面
Huh We got these three sides
有甲，乙，丙。讓我們分開
Got A, B, C. Let's split that
就在那裡
That's there
把這兩個帶走
Take these twos away Mmm
他不知道答案
He don't know the answer
因為這讓你很困惑
Because that's what confuses you
然後
And then
我意識到那是八！
I'm realizing what it is Eight!
答案是五
The answer's five
五點了
It's five
容易的
Easy
好吧，你看的是五平方
Okay, you're looking at five-squared
我在上面，我沒有時間
Me up here, I don't have time
我沒有時間為什麼我還要浪費時間？
I don't have time Why do I even waste my time?
我沒有時間浪費我的時間
I don't have time to waste my time
畢達哥拉斯定理很簡單
on the Pythagorean theorem It's simple
很簡單哇
It's simple Wow
太令人印象深刻了，泰迪
That is very impressive, Teddy
非常令人印象深刻
Very impressive
我期待著看到你在期中考試中表現如何
I look forward to seeing how you do on the midterm
我的期中考試
My midterm
好
All right
我們結束了嗎，斯圖爾特，
Are we done here, Stewart,
或者你想今晚教其餘的課嗎？
or do you want to teach the rest of the class for tonight?
繼續，嘉莉
Carry on, Carrie
我不喜歡他的態度
I don't like his attitude
你們都有一堂精彩的課
You all have a wonderful class
哦！什麼？
Oy! What?
天啊，那傢伙是個混蛋
God, that guy is a douchebag
我們只是要掩蓋事實嗎
Are we just gonna gloss over the fact
我們剛剛看了一場監獄爭鬥？
that we just watched a prison fight?
我們還剩下幾節課？
How many classes do we have left?
我現在實際上必須工作四個小時
I actually have to work for four hours right now
如果你願意，我可以十美元送你回家
I can give you a ride home for ten bucks, if you want
嘿，凱莉。嘿
Hey, Carrie. Hey
你做的真酷
That was real cool what you did
對我來說，在黑板上
for me in there at the blackboard
你知道，這就是我所說的
You know, that's what I was talking about
當我只是說要互相照顧的時候。
when I just say watching out for each other.
你知道，你抓我的背，我會抓你的？
You know, you scratch my back, I'll scratch yours?
哦，泰迪，不會再有背部抓痕了
Oh, there's not gonna be any more back-scratching, Teddy
那是最後一次
That's the last time that happens
你到底在董事會裡到底發生了什麼？
And what was really going on with you at the board anyways?
沒有任何東西
Nothing
不，我只是沒有準備好
No, I was just I wasn't prepared
如果你不想做這項工作，那就下課吧
If you're not gonna do the work, drop the class
你為什麼要...？不，凱莉
Why would you...? No, Carrie
嘿，我要做這項工作
Hey, I'm gonna do the work
你會看到的，我們會看到的
You'll see We'll see
是的，我們會很棒的
Yes, we will Great
極好的
Superb Excellent
很好
Good Mm-hmm
欺騙
Shit
親愛的，我回來了
Honey, I'm home
你睡著了嗎？
You sleeping?
你起來了？
You up?
對不起
Excuse me
戰利品看起來不錯，不是嗎？
Booty look good, don't it?
可惜你的臉會夾在書中間
Too bad your face gonna be in between them books
而不是臉頰
and not them cheeks
去學習
Go study
我不想學習
I don't want to study
嗯
Mmm
來吧，泰迪。集中
Come on, Teddy. Focus
集中精神，泰迪
Focus, Teddy
集中精神！
Focus!
你永遠不會得到它！
You'll never get it!
還給我！
Give it back!
嘿，夥計們，這是我的演示
Hey, guys, this is my demo
不管需要什麼，你知道
No matter what it takes, you know
我會一直戰鬥下去
I'm always gonna keep on fighting
我在戰鬥
I'm fighting
小麥克！你在做什麼?
Little Mac! What are you doing?
那是我的手機那些是我的筆記
That's my phone Those were my notes
你應該學習
You should be studying
到底怎麼回事？別像個混蛋
What the hell? Don't be such a dick
你會學習的！我恨你！
You're gonna study! I hate you!
那個比薩餅的周長是多少？
What's the circumference of that pizza?
直徑
The diameter
告訴我，比薩餅上有多少胡椒？
Just tell me, how many pepperonis on the pizza?
我給你一顆星
I'm giving you one star
我要把你送到一個糟糕的社區
I'm gonna drop you off here in a bad neighborhood
那怎麼樣？
How about that?
特裡薩！
Theresa!
現在是10點以後。你好！
It's after 10:00. Hello!
那是我的蘭迪
That's my Randy
世界上最可愛的人
Sweetest guy on earth
還有人想試試這個嗎？
Does anybody else want to try to take a crack at this?
我現在有點忙，嗯！
I'm kind of busy right now Mmm!
寶貝，你看到我的巫術了嗎？
Babe, you seen my Wite-Out?
什麼...？哦，不
What the...? Oh, hell no
屈麗娜
Trina
什麼，什麼，什麼，你現在有機器人側迪克了嗎？
What-what-what-what, you got robotic side dick now?
肥驢。
Fat asses.
你知道胖驢喜歡什麼嗎？
You know what fat asses like?
有真正工作的男人
Dudes that have a real job
泰迪！滾出去
Teddy! Get your ass out
泰迪，如果你沒有通過期中考試，
Teddy, if you don't pass that midterm,
沒有回家的女孩和你在一起
no way homegirl stays with you
嗯？
Huh?
想想看
Think about that
我們必須偷考試
We're gonna have to steal the test
驚歎聲
Whoa
思想融合了
Mind meld
我也是這麼想的
I was thinking the exact same thing
如果我們是真實的，
If we being real with it,
我需要盡可能多的幫助
I need as much help as I can get
從瓶蓋到斜邊等等，
Going from capping bottles to hypotenuses and all that,
我同樣被材料搞糊塗了
I'm just as confounded by the material
你們都感受到我了嗎？
as the rest of y'all Feel me?
我真的很不願意承認，但是語言障礙
I really hate to admit it, but with the language barrier
所有的提升動力都來自於我的腿，
and all the Lyft driving I've been doing,
我也在掙扎，夥計們
I'm struggling as well, guys
我覺得雀躍聽起來很有趣
I think a caper sounds fun
特裡薩，你什麼時候來的？
When'd you get here, Theresa?
哦，我一直都在這裡
Oh, I've been here the whole time
人們從未注意到我
People never notice me
它總是發生
It happens all the time It's
有點像超級大國，但是
kind of like a superpower, but
伴隨著極度孤獨的人
one that comes with a crushing loneliness
我很幸運。我真幸運
I'm blessed. I'm so blessed
是的，上帝很好
Yeah, God is good
嗯
Mm-hmm
行
Okay
嘿，米拉，你呢？
Hey, Mila, what about you?
我父母會很生氣的
My parents are gonna be really pissed
如果我再次被捕
if I get busted again
是的，我在我在
Yeah, I'm in I'm in
這就是我說的好吧
That's what I'm talking about All right
在我們這樣做之前，我只有一個問題
I just have one question before we do this
怎麼了？泰迪為什麼會這樣
What's up? Why does Teddy get to be
首要分子，夥計們？開始
the ringleader, guys? Come on
該死，路易斯，現在不行
Goddamn it, Luis Not now
我是說，說真的，夥計？這是他的主意
I mean, seriously, man? It was his idea
他比我們任何人都更瞭解這所學校
He knows this school better than any of us
啊。不要在意事實
Ah. Just never mind the fact
我偷偷溜進一個小地方
that I snuck into a little place
叫做美國
called America
哈！這是真的！
Ha! That's true!
路易斯今晚很熱
Luis is hot tonight
喲，T什麼？
Yo, T What?
我很感謝你帶來
I appreciate you bringing
這個神奇的，熾熱的撒旦雞
this amazing, blazing Satan chicken
好像很熱，但不是
It's like, it's hot, but it's not
我不喜歡辛辣的食物，但是這個
And I don't like spicy food, but this one
讓我告訴你還有什麼是熱的...你的呼吸
Let me tell you what else is hot... your breath
你為什麼那樣在我臉上呼吸？
Why are you breathing on the side of my face like that?
哦，你在我耳邊輕敲，夥計。停止
Oh You're smacking all in my ear, man. Stop
你還在打
You're still smacking
該死，你完蛋了，你完蛋了
Goddamn it, you're done You're done
你完了
You're done with that
真的嗎？
Really?
上帝，你有什麼問題？
God, what-what is your problem, man?
什麼？我說穿全黑。你為什麼不穿黑色？
What? I said wear all black. Why didn't you wear black?
洗衣日我所有的黑暗都在洗
Laundry day All my darks were in the wash
所以你穿黃色？
So you wore yellow?
很新鮮。很乾淨
It's fresh. It's clean
把你的胳膊從我臉上拿開
Get your get your arm out my face
滾出我的臉
Get out of my face
聚焦。走吧
Focus. Let's go
我們走吧
Let's go
喲，泰迪，演什麼，夥計？
Yo, Teddy, what's the play, man?
昨晚我看見看門人打掃衛生
Last night I saw the janitor cleaning
晚上8點左右斯圖爾特的辦公室
Stewart's office around 8:00 p.m
我明白了，那是內線，嗯？
I get it that's the inside man, huh?
不，鮑比，他不是我的內線
No, Bobby, he's not my inside man
他是看門人
He's the janitor
哦，媽的
Oh, shit
我要拿這個，我要拿
I got to take this, I got to take it
媽的
Sh-Shit
哦
Aw
不，不，不
No, no, no
嘿，寶貝
Hey, babe
嘿，寶貝，我想你
Hey, baby, I miss you
你還在工作嗎？
Are you still at work?
嗯，是的，是的，現在我在，呃，我在休息室
Uh, yeah, yeah, right now I'm in the, uh, I'm in the break room
我能參觀一下辦公室嗎？
Can I get a tour of the office?
如果我的孩子想去旅遊，那麼她可以去旅遊
If my baby wants a tour, then she can get a tour
你總是想看東西啊！
You always want to see something Ah!
如果我哦，泰迪
If I Oh, Teddy
嘿，泰迪，哦
Hey Teddy, oh
我們這裡有情況，我們有真實的
We got a situation here, we got a real
熱熔岩，熱熔岩什麼？嘿
Hot lava, hot lava What? Hey
好吧
Okay Um
哦，上帝，哦，上帝，哦，上帝，哦，上帝！
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God!
啊！世界衛生大會...？
Aah! Wha...?
天啊，烏龜頭伸出來了
God, turtle head sticking out
哦，那是一個大的，呃
Oh, that's a big one Uh
寶貝，那邊發生了什麼？哦，大狗屎
Babe, what is going on over there? Oh, big shit
親愛的，那是，呃，事實上
Honey, that's, uh, that's actually
那實際上是我的一個客戶經理
that's actually one of my account managers
辦公室裡到處都是個性
Personalities all over the office
呃，不停地笑
Uh, nonstop laughs
熾熱的熔岩！直達車
Hot lava! Nonstop
你知道我是怎麼做的
You know how I do
玩耍...在辦公室
play around... at the office
誰...？嘿，喲，怎麼了，兄弟？
Who's...? Hey, yo, what's up, bro?
你掛了我電話，夥計
You hung up on me, man
那是誰？那是我的，
Who's that? That's one of my,
那是我的一個客戶，就在那裡
that's one of my clients there, right there
是啊，我們正在檢查他的投資組合
Yeah, we were, we were going over his portfolio
看起來他在監獄裡
Kind of looks like he's in prison
哦，我的上帝，你真漂亮，寶貝
Oh, my God, you're so beautiful, baby
嗯，他看起來像那樣
Well, he looks like that
因為他是...內幕交易
cause he is... insider trading
他被錯誤地指控
He was wrongfully accused
你看起來像J洛和碧昂斯，媽媽
You're looking like J.Lo and Beyonce, mama
你介意帶我看看你的私處嗎？
Would you mind showing me your privates?
夠了，鮑比
Enough, Bobby
比如，轉過身來，讓我看看那個屁股，
Like, turn around, let me see that ass,
拜託，一點小妮子，什麼的
please, a little tit, something
對不起？
Excuse me?
我現在很強壯
I'm, like, really strong right now
就像，我可以對你做一些傳奇般的事情
Like, I could do things to you legendary shit
夠了，鮑比
Enough, Bobby
我會穿上大腿，但是，說真的，
I'll take some upper thigh, but, for real,
我真的很想看一些普納尼
I really want to see some punani
對不起？
Excuse me?
聽...哦，我的上帝
Listen... oh, my God
我不知道你在我身上放了什麼
I don't know what you put in me
它剛剛擊中了我
It just hit me
但是感覺像魔鬼！
But it feels like the Devil!
他說的話正好擊中了我，親愛的
It just hit me what he said, honey
他在說皮諾塔。
He's saying pinata.
夥計，我很久沒見到普納尼了
Man, I ain't see some punani in so long
鮑比喜歡打菠蘿
Bobby likes to hit pinatas
不！讓我...你知道我要做什麼嗎？
No! Let me... you know what I'm gonna do?
讓我，讓我給你回電話
Let me, let me call you back
我愛你，
Uh I love you,
我呢...等我結束了，我們就去旅遊
and I... we'll do the tour when I'm done
再見，寶貝
Bye, babe
那是什麼，鮑比？
What was that, Bobby?
喲，泰德，好看嗎，兄弟
Yo, Ted, good looking, bro
那是我未婚妻
That's my fiancee, man
你不要這樣和她說話
You don't talk to her like that
當我回到牢房時，我得到了傳說中的襪子
When I go back to the cell, I got the legendary socky-sock
你不會和我的女人談襪子吧
You're not having a sock session to my woman
那是不會發生的
That's, that's not going to happen
我要全力以赴
I'm going all out
好吧，你屁股裡有什麼，麥克？
Okay, what is in your ass, Mac?
饒了我吧，夥計
Cut me a break, man
我受夠了！
I've had enough!
等一下，我們有一個紅色的密碼
Hold on a second, we got a code red
我們有紅色代碼
We got a code red
泰迪，我沒有衛生紙
Teddy, I got no toilet paper
衛生紙，泰迪，曾經的我！
Toilet paper, Teddy, one-time me!
一次性的我！
One-time me!
泰迪！
Teddy!
好了，夥計們，聽著
All right, guys, listen
當看門人離開時，
When the janitor exits,
我們要出去，我們要抓住門
we're gonna go out, we're gonna catch the door
然後我們會悄悄地進去
And then we're gonna enter quietly
好吧好吧？
Okay Okay?
等一下
Wait a minute
巨無霸在哪裡？
Where's Big Mac?
我以為他和我們在一起
I thought he was with us
他
He
該死!
Damn it
他在做什麼？
What's he doing?
哦，我的上帝，你在做什麼？
Oh, my God What are you doing?
來吧，來吧，來吧，來吧，麥克！
Come on, come on, come on, come on Mac!
媽的，它奏效了哦，我的上帝！
Holy shit, it worked Oh, my God!
麥克！
Mac!
你剛剛殺了他嗎？
Did you just kill him?
不，我沒有殺他
No, I didn't kill him
我把他掐死了
I just choked him out
你說沒有證人
You said no witnesses
我什麼時候說過的？
When did I say that?
你沒這麼說？
You didn't say that?
哦，上帝
Oh, God
你知道嗎？
You know what?
我的信號被越過了
I got my signals crossed
有很多指示，泰迪
There's a lot of instructions, Teddy
我什麼也沒說
I didn't say anything about
你知道嗎？你會解決這個問題的
You know what? You are going to fix this
你聽到了嗎，麥克？你要把屍體藏起來
Do you hear me, Mac? You're gonna hide this body
砍他？隱藏
Chop him up? Hide
燒掉它？藏起來
Burn it? Hide it
砍、燒、埋？
Chop, burn, bury?
嘿。有人有什麼消息嗎？不
Hey. Anybody got anything? No
好吧，Mila，我們看起來怎麼樣？
All right, Mila, how we looking?
繼續看
Keep looking
吸我的蛋蛋，泰迪！欺騙
Suck my balls, Teddy! Shit
媽的，你應該看看你的臉
Shit You should've seen your face
你看起來很可笑噓！
You look ridiculous Shh!
好吧，我把屍體藏起來，
All right, I stashed the body,
如果上帝願意，他幾小時後就會醒來
and God willing, he'll wake up in a couple hours
此外，棒球教練主要人物，
Also, that baseball coach principal guy,
他在路上
he's on his way
什麼？你為什麼不帶頭呢？
What? Why wouldn't you lead with that?
該死。這是家長會
Damn. It's the PTA meeting
哦，媽的
Oh, shit
特裡薩，你起來了
Theresa, you're up
什麼？什麼？我聽我說
What? What? I Listen to me
好吧，我需要你出去，
Okay I need you to go out there,
我需要你停下來
and I need you to stall
哦，不，不，不，不，不，我不能調情
Oh, no, no, no, no I can't flirt
我不知道我有什麼舉動，我不需要
I-I don't know any moves I-I don't need that
從1996年開始，我就沒有調情了，即使在那時，
I haven't flirted since like 1996, and even then,
這就像給警察一個方便的機會
it was like offering to give the cop a handy
從超速罰單上下來，猜猜看
to get off a speeding ticket, and guess what
他沒有接受，我不擅長
He didn't take it I'm bad at it
這不是我要你做的
That's not what I'm asking you to do
在我的時代，這真的是無辜的
In my day, it was really innocent
現在一切都是關於屁股的
Now it's all about the butt
前幾天我聽到一個人說，
I heard a guy the other day say,
我要像核桃一樣敲碎屁股。
I'm gonna crack that butt like a walnut.
什麼？那是什麼意思？
What? What does that even mean?
你為什麼要從那裡開始？得了
Why would you start there? Stop it
你不想從前面開始嗎？
Wouldn't you want to start in the front?
特裡薩，聽著，以一個很好的傳教立場，
Theresa, listen With a nice missionary position,
你知道，一些溫柔的撫摸
you know, some gentle touching
在我的日子裡，也許你一生中有一次，
In my day, maybe once in your lifetime,
你可能會得到一個小拇指的末端，
you might get the end of a pinky,
這是一生中最激動人心的事，好嗎？
and that was the thrill of a lifetime, okay?
住手，這是很多信息
Stop it That's a lot of information
我不需要知道
that I did not need to know
是的，那是很多
Yeah, that was a lot
去談談烘焙銷售
Go talk about bake sales
媽媽的東西。不是，不是屁股的東西是的，媽媽的東西
Mom stuff. Not-not butt stuff Yeah, mom stuff
去媽媽那裡，我-我試試。我試試
Go mom it I-I'll try. I'll try
好嗎？好吧，我能做到
Okay? Okay I can do that
去吧，去吧，明白了。行
Go, go Got it. Okay
媽的。路易斯，在她放之前出去
Shit. Luis, go out there before she puts
她屁股裡有東西好嗎
something in her butt Okay
好嗎？
Okay?
你在做什麼，麥克？
What are you doing, Mac?
尋找活板門
Looking for trapdoors
我很高興你在這裡，麥克
I'm glad you're here, Mac
請先寄給我
Send it to me first, please
對，對，我們可以給你發郵件
Right, right We can e-mail you the rest
因為我只想謝謝你
Cause I just want to Thank you
那太好了，我會派人出去
That would be great I'll send out
今晚的電子郵件，好嗎？是的。非常感謝你
that e-mail tonight, okay? Yeah. Thank you so much
好的，再見，安全開車回家
Okay, bye Drive home safe
哦，嘿
Oh, hey
你好
Hi
謝謝你召開這次偉大而精彩的會議
Thank you for that great, wonderful meeting
對不起，我認識你嗎？
I'm sorry, do I know you?
我在裡面。記得嗎？
I was in there. Remember?
是的，是的，是的，是的
Yes, yes, yes, yes
嗨。豪頓夫人不，你，呃，只是
Hi. Mrs. Howerton No, you, uh, just
豪頓太太。是的，當然
Mrs. Howerton. Yes, of course
不，你提出了幾個引人注目的問題
No, you brought up, uh, several compelling issues
我當然知道
I sure did
嗯，我能幫你什麼嗎？
Well, what can I help you with?
她很討厭這個。快點，我快到了
She sucks at this. Hurry I'm almost there
所以我的孩子得到了一份關於太陽系的作業，
So my child gets an assignment about the solar system,
這是一個立體圖，
and it's to make a diorama,
他不知道如何製作立體佈景
and he doesn't know how to make a diorama
我是那個拿著熱膠槍的人
I'm the one with the hot glue gun
半夜11 : 00
in the middle of the night it's 11:00 p.m
我的意思是，別誤會，我們很幸運能去
I mean, don't get me wrong, we're blessed to go to
學校在這裡，但我很抱歉，我必須走了
school here, but I'm I'm sorry, I have to go
好嗎？我會打電話給我的辦公室。-快點
Okay? Call my office I will. - Hurry up
我要走了，我要冷靜下來
I'm going, I'm going Calm down
來吧，米拉
Come on, Mila
你提出了一些偉大的觀點，
You've made some great points,
但是我現在必須走了晚安
but I have to go now Good night
等一下，謝謝。我得走了
Wait a minute Thank you. I have to go
好吧，我真的得走了，等等。不
Okay, I really have to go Wait. No
等等，等等，等等什麼？
Wait, wait, wait What?
哦！你沒事吧？
Oh! Are you okay?
我感到頭暈
I feel faint
好吧，我們給你弄些水來
Well, let's get you some water
你是嗎...？謝謝你抓住我
Are you...? Thanks for catching me
當然。你沒事吧？
Of course. Are you all right?
i
I
你癲癇發作了嗎？
Are you having a seizure?
你牙齒裡有什麼東西嗎？
Do you have something in your teeth?
我希望我的牙齒裡有你不，不，不，不，不，不
I wish I had you in my teeth No, no, no, no, no, no
好吧，不，我沒有意識到這是什麼
Okay, no, I didn't realize that's what this was
不，謝謝，女士，溫柔的撫摸
No, thank you, ma'am Gentle touching
我是你孩子學校的校長
I am the principal of your child's school
我得走了，好嗎？i
I have to walk away now, okay? I
我沒有愛情，請
I'm in a loveless marriage Please
我不參與這件事！
I am not participating in this!
你不必參加專業
You don't have to participate To a professional
我會做的，我會做所有的工作
I'll do it I'll do all the work
不，我會做的
No, I'm I'll do it all
如果你只是女士
If you just Ma'am
...看著我的眼睛
...look me in the eyes
夫人，夫人
Ma'am, ma'am
不合適，好嗎？
Not appropriate, okay?
好了，在這裡，好了？
Okay, here it is Okay?
如果這就是你想要的
If this is what you want
這就是你的問題所在
This is what it's about with you
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，我沒有看
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm not looking
像核桃一樣把它敲開
Crack it open like a walnut
謝謝你。不，謝謝你像核桃一樣把堅果敲碎
Thank you. No, thank you Crack that nut like a walnut
謝謝你。不，謝謝
Thank you. No, thank you
打開那個堅果謝謝
Crack that nut open Thank you
不，謝謝你像男人對待女人一樣
No, thank you Do what men do with women's asses
哦，夥計
Oh, man
輕點它！我不能
Just tap it! I can't
我不能站在這裡，好嗎？
I can't stand here for this, okay?
好好享受吧晚安
Give it a crack Good night
來吧，給它一些
Come on, give it some
哦，那太難了
Oh, that was so hard
她非常想要你
She wanted you so bad
但是你不能去那裡
But you can't go there
校長有原則
Principals have principles
嗯。哦，但是你認識史泰威
Mmm. Oh, but you know Stewie
會把屁股撕了！
would've tore that ass up, though!
不是黑色的聲音
Not a black voice
讓我們看看
Let's see
喂？喂？
Hello? Hello?
這裡有人嗎？
Somebody in here?
我有球棒
I have a bat
我不怕用它
And I'm not afraid to use it
如果有人在這裡，
If there is someone in here,
你擅自闖入
you are trespassing
我完全在我的權利範圍內
And I am well within my rights
為自己辯護
to defend myself
所以出來吧，
So come on out,
我不會打你的頭
and I won't bash your head
救命！
Help!
外面有人嗎？
Anybody out there?
帶我離開這裡！
Get me out of here!
驚歎聲
Whoa
好吧，怎麼回事，麥克？
Okay What the hell, Mac?
你說得對，麥克
That was close You're damn right it was, Mac
我想知道為什麼
I wonder why
是的，我...因為我打噴嚏了
Yeah, I... well, it's 'cause I sneezed
我知道你做了什麼
I know what you did
什麼？
What?
我明白了
I got it
我真的試過我甚至做過屁股的事
I really tried I even did the butt stuff
我告訴過你不要做屁股的事
I told you don't do the butt stuff
我不知道，fam，可能有用
I don't know, fam, might've worked
看起來他可能把抽屜弄髒了，真的
Looked like he might've sauced his drawers, real talk
他什麼？
He what?
他被打開了
He-he was turned on
真的嗎？
Really?
媽的，我也是
Shit, I was, too
嘿
Hey
謝謝，傑倫
Thanks, Jaylen
你有一種環保的感覺
You got that little eco-friendly vibe going
什麼是生態友好的？
What's eco-friendly?
很少浪費
Very little waste
哦，我以為你指的是她的灌木叢
Oh, I thought you meant her bush
不，哦，你知道嗎？我同意
No. Oh, you know what? I'm with that
嘿，現在！
Hey, now!
好的，傑倫，傑倫！
Okay, Jaylen, Jaylen!
我們得走了，你們。我們走吧
We gotta go, y'all. Let's go
是啊，我們走吧，來吧，來吧
Yeah, let's go Come on, come on
欺騙
Shit
誰在外面？
Who's out there?
誰來幫我
Somebody help me, please
發生什麼事了？
What happened?
我不知道有人從後面抓住了我
I don't know Someone grabbed me from behind
把我扔進污水池
and threw me in the slop sink
遊戲臉，朗尼
Game face, Lonnie
我們被封鎖了
We're on lockdown
啊，是啊！
Ah, yeah!
那會得到他的嘿！
That'll get him Hey!
哦，該死的，走，走，走！-嘿！
Oh, shit Go, go, go! - Hey!
欺騙
Shit
我們該怎麼辦...？嘿，媽的
What do we...? Hey Shit
哦。嘿，鮑比
Oh. Hey, Bobby
鮑比，這是真的，夥計，我們該怎麼辦？
Bobby, shit just got real, man, what do we do?
夥計，我不知道，只是不要被槍殺，兄弟
Man, I don't know, just don't get shot, bro
你什麼意思，不被槍斃？
What do you mean, don't get shot?
鮑比，你應該是個頑固的罪犯，夥計
Bobby, you're supposed to be a hardened criminal, man
那不可能是你的建議
That can't be your advice
鮑比，你去監獄幹什麼？
What the hell'd you go to jail for, Bobby?
我搶了全食，兄弟
I robbed Whole Foods, bro
我搶了全食
I robbed Whole Foods
那是你的罪行？
That's your crime?
你因為偷了15美元的萵苣而進了監獄？
You went to jail for stealing $15 lettuce?
不，兄弟，你在睡覺
No, bro, you're sleeping
我白天搬了一些可樂和毒品，但是我的羽衣甘藍遊戲
I moved some coke and some dope in the day, but my kale game
我的羽衣甘藍遊戲不
my kale game No
現在，這是卑鄙的！
Now, that's mean!
草餵牛肉
Grass-fed beef
你對沒有自由放養的雞一無所知
You don't know nothing about no free-range chicken
暴徒生活！傑倫，冷靜...安靜
Thug life! Jaylen, calm... calm down
我把所有的農貿市場都搞砸了不，不
And I had all the farmer markets on smash No, no
你不用解釋
You don't get to explain
你沒必要說髒話...再見
You don't get to expla... Bye
好吧，你們，這邊
All right, y'all, this way
注意，入侵者
Attention, intruders
這是帕特斯基校長
This is Principal Patowsky
安全門被鎖上了，無路可逃
The exit doors are locked down There is no escape
我不敢相信我們會因為GED練習考試而死去
I-I can't believe we're gonna die over a GED practice test
這甚至不是真正的測試聽著
It's not even a real test Listen
我這樣做只是為了走出家門
I just did this to get out of the house
我以為這會很有趣
I thought this was gonna be fun
你知道，我們會破門而入
You know, we're gonna break in
閉嘴！閉嘴！
Just shut up! Just shut up!
閉嘴！該死的！
Shut up! Goddamn!
整天都在談論你的孩子和一切！
Been talking about your kids and everything all day!
現在不是時候
This ain't the time
現在，你們把它拉在一起
Now, y'all pull it together
我們很好
We are fine
我們...我們沒事
We-we... we are okay
屋頂。我們去屋頂吧
The roof. Let's hit the roof
好吧，當我在這裡上學的時候，
Okay, when I went to school here,
這就是我們離開學校的原因
that's how we got out of school
然後我們會跳到小學屋頂上
And then we would jump onto the elementary school roof
來吧！
Come on!
移動它，移動它！這是個壞主意
Move it, move it! This is a bad idea
來吧！這是個壞主意！
Come on! This is a bad idea!
小心，小心，哇，哇！
Watch it, watch it Whoa, whoa!
哇，哇！哇！
Whoa, whoa! Whoa!
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa Whoa
哦，我的上帝，哇，哇！
Oh, my God Whoa, whoa!
好，退後
Okay, back up
聽我說，來吧！
Listen to me Come on!
向你發誓，當我在這裡上學的時候，
Swear to you, when I went to school here,
那一跳似乎沒有那麼高
that jump did not seem that high
我不可能做到這一點
There's no way I can make that
我能跳三英尺，膝蓋和背部
I can jump like three feet My knees and my back
都是從移動的盒子裡拍出來的，泰迪！
are totally shot from moving boxes, Teddy!
好吧，我們該怎麼辦？
All right What are we gonna do?
我們該怎麼辦？聽著，聽著
What are we gonna do? Listen, listen
我拿到了
I got it
假設它有15英尺高
Let's just say it's 15 feet
哦，上帝
Oh, God
走15英尺，
Take that 15 feet,
減去你能跳的三英尺
minus the three feet that you can jump
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
我們所要做的就是使用畢達哥拉斯定理
All we gotta do is use the Pythagorean theorem
課堂上沒人在聽
Nobody was listening in class
沒人知道怎麼做哦，我的上帝
Nobody knows how to do that Oh, my God
不，等等，等等，嘉莉說...嘉莉說，
No, wait, wait, wait Carrie said... Carrie said,
為了完成畢達哥拉斯定理，
in order to do the Pythagorean theorem,
你必須知道斜邊
you-you have to know the hypotenuse
我們所要做的就是降低血壓
All we gotta do is hypotenuse it
A平方加B平方等於C平方
A-squared plus B-squared equals C-squared
如果你知道...知道兩面，
If you know... know two sides,
那會幫助你找到第三個，
then that'll help you figure out the third,
所以大約有六英尺寬，
so it's roughly six feet across,
15平方是225除以6平方
and 15-squared is 225 divided by six-squared
斜邊！等等，我剛才說了什麼？
Hypotenuse it! Wait, what did I just say?
是36歲，是的，36歲
It's 36 Yeah, 36
但是你沒有分割它，你添加它
But you don't divide it You add it
那麼，我剛才說了什麼？呃...呃
So, what did I just say? The, um... the, uh
她是數學最好的。等等，不，呃
She's the best one at math Wait, no, uh
斜邊！不，不，你可以這樣做
Hypotenuse it! No, no, you can do this
那麼，乘以6平方...我不知道不
By six-squared, then... I-I don't know No
不，來吧。你有這個嗎
No, come on. You got this
哦，我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
米拉！哦，我的上帝！
Mila! Oh, my God!
哦！
Oh!
你沒事吧？夥計們！
You all right? Guys!
這不是一個難的數學問題
It's not a hard math problem
這是一個簡單的物理問題
It's a simple physics problem
跳
Just jump
你斜邊了嗎？
Did you did you hypotenuse it?
是的，我斜邊了
Yeah, I hypotenused it
你能跳下去嗎？
Can you just jump?
麥克，你是下一個
Mac, you're up next
不，不，是的
No. No Yes
麥克，你不要給我那個，好嗎？
Mac, don't you give me that, okay?
當我想到男人，我想到你
When I think man, I think you
我想小麥克一定有多驕傲
I think about how proud Little Mac must be
我要你做你最擅長的事情
I want you to do what you do best
然後變得偉大
and go be great
好吧。是
Okay. Yeah
穿過屋頂，麥克
Get across that roof, Mac
是啊！好吧！好嗎？
Yeah! Okay! All right?
好吧，你明白了
All right You got this
麥克進來了！退後！
Mac coming in! Step back!
走吧，麥克，謝謝你，泰迪
Let's go, Mac Thank you, Teddy
隨時
Any time
麥克攻擊！
Mac attack!
孤獨之心的主人
Owner of a lonely heart
媽的！
Shit!
哦，上帝！
Oh, God!
哦，泰迪！
Oh, Teddy!
哦，我為什麼要聽你的？欺騙
Oh, why'd I listen to you? Shit
你太有說服力了！
You were so convincing!
對不起，夥計嘿
I'm sorry, buddy Hey
我的手臂有點刺痛
My arm's kind of tingly
我想我可能傷害了它
I think I might have hurt it
感覺很奇怪，夥計
Feels weird, man
他該死的肩膀在嘴裡
His damn shoulder is in his mouth
哦！
Oh!
嘿
Hey
巨無霸，夥計，對此我很抱歉
Big Mac, man, I'm sorry about that
那只熱雞，有點倒帶，夥計
That hot chicken, it just kind of got on rewind, man
要麼是後面，要麼是前面，
It was either the back or the front,
我剛買了這條褲子，fam
and I just got these pants, fam
哦，上帝，我度過了最糟糕的夜晚！
Oh, God, I'm having the worst night!
你好，泰迪
Hello, Teddy
嗯？
Huh?
嘿，寶貝
Hey, babe
你不需要嘿，寶貝我
You don't need to hey, babe me
我知道發生了什麼
I know what's going on
什麼，呃，嗯
What's, uh, um
怎麼回事？
What's going on?
深夜？
The late hours?
秘密？
The secrecy?
承認吧，泰迪
Just admit it, Teddy
承認什麼？
Just admit what?
這很明顯
It's so obvious
你越來越冷了
You're getting cold feet
是啊！
Yeah!
冷腳？
Cold feet?
自從你求婚後，你就不再是你自己了
Ever since you proposed, you haven't been yourself
冷腳？
Cold feet?
麗莎，我不會退縮
Lisa, I am not getting cold feet
事實上，這是完全相反的
In fact, it's the it's the complete opposite
我的腳很暖和
My feet are very warm
我想要這個
I want this
我道歉
And I apologize
如果事情是這樣，我道歉
I apologize if things have been
最近有點瘋狂，但是，寶貝，
a little crazy as of late, but, babe,
你必須知道我在外面
you gotta know that I am out here
我......我在努力
I'm-I'm... I'm trying
好嗎？我每天晚上都在拚命工作，
Okay? I am busting my ass every day, every night,
對我們來說
for us
為了我和你
For me and you
我在外面的另一個世界，寶貝
I'm in a different world out there, babe
這個世界讓我很緊張
And this world is stressing me out
這讓我很緊張
It is stressing me out
對不起，我懷疑你
I'm sorry I doubted you
我知道這種職業變化很大
I-I know this career change has been a lot
太多了
It's a lot
It's so much
太多了
It's so, so much
可憐的孩子
Poor baby
我愛你哦
I love you Oh
我也愛你
I love you, too
這能完成你的訂單嗎？
Does that complete your order?
哦，等等，等等
Oh, wait, h-hold up
我不想要那個蘋果派是的，我不能...對不起
I don't want that apple pie Yeah, I can't... I'm sorry
很難聽到你的聲音
It's-it's kind of hard to hear you
背景中有一個嬰兒
There's a baby in the background
寶貝，我說安靜點坐下！
Baby, I said be quiet Sit down!
是啊，說——再給我說一遍
Yeah, say-say it one more time for me
說吧...再說一遍，那漢堡好吃嗎？
Say it... say it again Is that burger good or what?
有什麼辦法能讓你尊敬我嗎
Is there any way I can get you to respectfully
把孩子關起來？你說什麼？
shut that baby up? What'd you say?
把車開到窗戶邊去吧，為了愛情見鬼去吧！
Just pull up to the window, for the love Heck no!
哦。欺騙
Oh. Shit
媽的，行不通
Shit It won't work
我看到你了，泰迪
I see you, Teddy
它不起作用了
It's not working
汽水機後面的泰迪·沃克
Teddy Walker behind the soda machine
喂？欺騙
Hello? Shit
我看見你在看泰迪·沃克
Teddy Walker I see you looking at
我們正在進行眼神交流
We're making eye contact right now
睜開你的眼睛，泰迪
Open your eyes, Teddy
泰迪，過來！斯圖爾特
Teddy, come here! Stewart
嘿
Hey
斯圖爾特，你是說泰迪？
Stewart, you were saying Teddy?
大約十倍
About ten times
嘿嘿
Hey Hey
幫我個忙
Do me a favor Yep
呃，去那邊處理這個情況
Uh, go over there and handle that situation
在免下車的地方
at the drive-through Uh-huh
之後我會告訴你該怎麼做，
And I'll tell you what to do after that,
因為我負責
because I'm in charge
嘿，你好？
Hey, so Hello?
給我一秒鐘。女士
Give me a second. M-Ma'am
我說過我不想要餡餅好吧，女士，女士
I said I didn't want the pie Okay, ma'am, ma
她不想要餡餅
She don't want the pie Uh-uh
把餡餅拿開她想拿
Take the pie off She want to get the
我說過我不會得到餡餅
I said I ain't getting a pie
拉上來！你聽到了嗎
Pull up! You heard me
把車開到窗戶邊！好
Pull up to the window! All right
當她停下來的時候，告訴我，
When she pull up, tell me,
因為我要來打孩子的臉
cause I'm gonna come punch the baby in the face
上帝看不到一切，只要讓我知道
God don't see everything Just let me know
嘿，跟我說話，你好嗎？
Hey, talk to me, man How you doing?
你知道，我以為是伍德布裡奇朋克
You know, I thought it was the Woodbridge punks
闖入學校，但現在一切都有意義了
that broke into the school, but now it all makes sense
我找到了這個
I found this
在犯罪現場
at the scene of the crime
那麼，你做了什麼，嗯？
So, what'd you do, huh?
闖入我的電腦？
Break into my computer?
偷期中考試？
Steal the midterm?
有點偏執吧，斯圖？
Being a little paranoid, aren't we, Stew?
我是嗎？斯圖爾特，那是一個塑料袋
Am I? Stewart, that's a plastic bag
裡面有雞皮，上面有證據
with a chicken wrapper in it with the word evidence
寫在上面，這可能是你的筆跡
written on it, which is probably in your handwriting
這不是一把冒煙的槍，斯圖
It's not exactly a smoking gun, Stew
這只是巧合，對吧？
It's just a coincidence, right?
或許
Probably
如果你偷了那個測試，
If you stole that test,
我會發現的，泰迪
I will find out, Teddy
我是一個誠實的人，努力過著誠實的生活
I'm an honest man trying to make an honest living
泰迪·沃克不作弊
Teddy Walker does not cheat
你作弊
You cheated
你們每一個人
Every last one of you
欺騙
cheated
呃...驚歎聲
Uh... whoa
凱莉，這些都是非常強烈的指控
Carrie, those are very strong accusations
真的。比如，什麼？
For real. Like, what?
我被冒犯了
I'm offended
好吧，我會記下來的，泰迪
Well, I'll take note of that, Teddy
你們誰想承認呢？
Which one of you want to own up to it?
我也很生氣
I'm offended, too
鮑比？
Bobby?
你是罪犯
You a criminal
你顯然不擅長
You obviously not good at it
這就是你進監獄的原因
That's why you in jail
這一切都是你策劃的嗎？
Did you orchestrate this whole thing?
我的意思是，你為什麼要挑我的毛病，描述我？
I mean, why you gonna pick on me and profile me?
我是唯一一個被鎖在這裡的人
I'm the only one locked up here
所以，如果我被鎖在這裡，
So, if I'm locked up in here,
我怎麼能在外面偷考試呢，嘉莉小姐？
how can I be out there stealing the test, Miss Carrie?
哦，哦，等等
Oh, oh, wait a minute
你們都偷了考試？
Y'all stole the test?
我沒說什麼
I'm not saying nothing
我什麼都不知道
I don't know nothing
I don't know shit
因為我什麼也沒說
Cause I never said nothing
關於有人偷考試的事
about anybody stealing the test
我們就要瞭解真相了
We're about to get to the truth
誰偷了考試？
Who stole the test?
麥克？
Mac?
你想向我解釋一下你是如何得到滿分的？
You want to explain to me how you got a perfect score?
事情是這樣的，好嗎？
Here's the thing, all right?
我知道我沒有得到滿分，
I know I didn't get a perfect score,
因為我故意錯過了一些
because I missed a few on purpose
哦，軟糖
Oh, fudge
謝謝你！
Thank you!
你是告密者，麥克
You's a snitch, Mac
告密者是婊子
Snitches are bitches
我不喜歡騙子
I don't like cheaters
我討厭我教一個滿是騙子的房間
And I hate that I am teaching a room full of cheaters
我不喜歡騙子
I don't like men that cheat
我不喜歡欺騙的女人
I don't like women that cheat
我甚至不跟政客打交道
I don't even deal with politicians
你知道為什麼嗎？因為他們都是騙子
You know why? Cause they all cheaters
我甚至不吃奇多
I don't even eat Cheetos
你知道為什麼嗎？因為聽起來像騙子。
You know why? 'Cause it sound like cheaters.
再加上奇托灰塵會給你特朗普的顏色
Plus that Cheeto dust will give you that Trump color
是啊，很難得到奇多灰塵
Yeah It's hard to get that Cheeto dust
放開你的手
off your hands
這會毀了你的女兒
It'll mess up your Girbauds
你知道，我起初喜歡你
You know, I liked you at first
你們都完了
I'm done with all of y'all
你們都可以從我的課上起床
All of y'all can get up out my class
我和你們都玩完了什麼？
I'm done with y'all What?
好吧，凱莉，讓我說點什麼
Okay, Carrie, let me I want to say something
我的GED呢？他將從高中退學
What about my GED? He's gonna drop out of high school
如果我得不到GED，我就要坐牢
If I don't get my GED, I'm going to prison
我需要這個GED
I need this GED
你需要把你的戰利品關起來
You need to keep your booty closed
這就是你在監獄裡需要做的
That's what you need to do You in jail
不，我需要這個GED
No, I need this GED
我們不能靠蘭迪的工資生活
We can't live on Randy's salary
請不要讓我回家
Please don't make me go home
我討厭我的孩子
I hate my kids
但是我喜歡當媽媽
But I love being a mom
我很幸運。我真幸運
I'm blessed. I'm so blessed
凱莉，拜託
Carrie, please
我不能活一輩子
I cannot live a lifetime
開著花冠在醉鬼周圍兜風
of driving around drunks in a Corolla
聽著，我最不想做的事
Look, the last thing I want to do
正在貝斯特韋斯特酒店打掃房間
is be cleaning the rooms at the Best Western
好嗎？因為這一切
Okay? 'Cause all that
尤其是短期房間，
Especially them short-stay rooms,
因為你知道那是什麼，對吧？
cause you know what that is, right?
那只是會用到避孕套，髒床單
That's just gonna be used condoms, soiled sheets
那不是你在哪裡遇到你的賤女人的地方嗎？
Ain't that where you met your bottom bitch at?
你認識屈麗娜？
You know Trina?
嗯
Mm-hmm
她屁股也很胖
She got a fat ass, too
你知道嗎？你們都有一些傷感的故事，
You know what? All of you got little sob stories,
但是你們都應該想到這一點
but y'all should've thought about that
在你去偷考試之前
before you went and stole the test
滾出我的課堂
Just get the hell up out of my class
這不是悲傷的故事。不！
It's not sob stories. No!
我...我是那個想讓我的生活變得和諧的人
I'm-I'm the one who wants to get my life together
讓我給你講講傑伊
Let-let-let me tell you something about Jay
出去！
Get out!
出去！出去！
Get out! Get out!
你們都是我
All of y'all It was me
我呢...嘿
And I... Hey
是我
It was me
不應該生他們的氣
Shouldn't be mad at none of them
我的意思是，是的，他們看了答案，
I mean, yeah, they looked at the answers,
但是如果我沒有把它放在他們的腿上，他們就不會有
but they wouldn't have if I hadn't put it on their lap
我要為這一切負責
I take responsibility for it all
我是策劃整件事的主謀
I was the mastermind I orchestrated the whole thing
都是我
It was all me
謝謝你
Thank you
謝謝你，泰迪
Thank you, Teddy
我欣賞你的誠實
I appreciate your honesty
我只是想做正確的事，嘉莉
I'm just trying to do what's right, Carrie
現在你可以離開我的班級了
Now you can get the hell out of my class
嗯？
Huh?
上路吧，傑克
Hit the road, Jack
不要讓門把手打到上帝劈開你的地方
Don't let the doorknob hit you where the good Lord split you
我想當我說這些話時，
I thought that when I said all that stuff,
你會聽的
that you would listen to it
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
你在這裡沒有第二次機會了
You gets no second chances up in here
不再和我在一起了
Not with me no more
呃。我不再支持你了
Uh-uh. I ain't got your back no more
你甚至不想在這裡我真的想在這裡
You don't even want to be here I do want to be here
泰迪，你甚至不想在這裡
You don't even want to be here, Teddy
不，至於你們其他人，
No And as for the rest of you,
我想讓你長時間的努力思考
I want you to think long and hard
如果你真的想要這個
about if you really want this
下課
Class dismissed
找到解決方案...
Find a solution for the...
我什麼都不知道
I don't know none of this shit
我需要你
I need you
我需要你的幫助把手放下
I need your help Put your damn hand down
我要在彩虹關閉前去
I'm going to Rainbows before they close
這是情感購物，嘉莉
That's emotional shopping, Carrie
這是彩虹，混蛋
It's Rainbows, motherfucker
狗屎很便宜
Shit is cheap
泰迪，泰迪，泰迪
Teddy, Teddy, Teddy
你真蠢
You are stupid
直到你承認，她才知道發生了什麼
She didn't know what was going on until you admitted it
我們讓她一直到最後，
We had her right up till the end,
然後是泰迪，舊磚頭
and then Teddy, old brick head
哦，泰迪！
Oh, Teddy!
你活該
You deserved that
學校？
A school?
我們從未接受過這樣的項目
We've never taken on a project like that
嗯，我是一個開箱即用的思想家
Well, I am an outside-of-the-box thinker
這就是我
That's just who I am
我認為如果學生很興奮
I think that if students are excited
關於他們的環境，
about their environment,
他們會對學習感到興奮
they'll be excited about learning
這完全有道理
That makes total sense
我知道我會的
I know I would
我很高興聽到這個消息
Well, I'm glad to hear it
如果你感興趣，我願意給你
If you're interested, I'd love to give you
參觀學校
a tour of the school
你可以隨時來，或者你知道，
You could come by any day, or you know what,
你甚至可以放學後來
you could even come after school
我們還有幾個夜間節目
We have several night programs as well
嘿嘿
Hey Hey
好，給我看看你有什麼
Okay, show me what you got
給我看看你有什麼！
Show me what you got!
你有什麼給我的？開始
What you got for me? Come on
點燃。你有什麼？
Light up. What you got?
哦，你殺了我！
Oh, you killing me!
你贏了。恭喜
You won. Congratulations
我為你感到驕傲，boo
I'm proud of you, boo
現在，你打敗你的老師並不酷
Now, it's not cool that you beat your teacher
在德克薩斯舉行，但我喜歡這種方式
at Texas hold 'em, but I like the way
你把計算結果釘在了底池賠率上，
you nailed down the calculations on the pot odds,
所以我讓這張幻燈片
so I'm gonna let this slide
現在，記住我說過的話
Now, remember what I said
沒有捷徑可走，你必須全力以赴
There are no shortcuts You gotta work your butt off
好嗎？給我一些愛
Okay? Give me some love
嗯。真為你驕傲
Mmm. So proud of you
繼續，祝你今天愉快
Go on and have a good day, now
也許有一天，我會帶你去拉斯維加斯
Maybe one day, I'll take you to Vegas
很酷
That was cool
你知道，呃，這曾經是特殊的ed教室
You know, uh, this used to be the special ed classroom
當我來到這裡
when I went here
它仍然是
It still is
你教特殊教育？
You teach special ed?
特殊教育是我的一部分
Special ed is one of my sections
事實上，這是我的最愛之一
It's one of my favorites, actually
你知道，那孩子讓我想起了我自己
You know, that kid reminds me a lot of myself
我根本不會做數學
I couldn't do math for shit
當我在學校的時候
when I was in school
不同的是我沒有像你這樣的老師
Difference is I didn't have a teacher like you
願意留下來幫我的人
that was willing to stay behind and help me
我知道你在做什麼，泰迪
I know what you're doing, Teddy
我承認你很酷
And I admit it was very cool of you
為你的同學承擔秋天的責任，
to take the fall for your classmates,
但是你是個騙子
but you're a hustler
試著不做工作就溜過去
Trying to skate by without doing the work
你應該知道你不能逼我
You should know you can't hustle me
我願意
I do
好嗎？我知道
Okay? I-I do know that
我向你保證，我完了
And I promise you I'm done
我不要再忙碌了
I'm not hustling no more
夜校是第二次機會
Night school is about second chances
如果我沒有第二次機會，
And if I don't get this second chance,
那我就結束了
then it's over for me
夜校是我僅有的
Night school is all that I have
請
Please
我會考慮一個條件
I'll consider it on one condition
不管是什麼
Whatever it is
我們讓你接受測試
We get you tested
性病？這不是問題
For STDs? That's not an issue
我不介意。我是說
I don't mind that. I mean
該死的
Goddamn it
有一次，
There was one time where, uh,
避孕套爆了，因為我把球放進去了
the condom popped 'cause I put my balls inside of
不，你這個白癡
No, you idiot
學習障礙
For learning disabilities
沒人在乎你和你的婊子們的出軌
Nobody cares about your escapades with your bitches
那麼，測試結果是什麼呢？
So, what are the test results,
凱莉？
Carrie?
泰迪，問題是
Teddy, the issue is
你臨床上很笨
you're clinically dumb
我就知道
I knew it
我知道這是一個錯誤，我知道這是一個錯誤
I knew it was a mistake I knew it was a mistake
男孩，對不起，我只是打擾你
Boy, I'm sorry I'm just messing with you
來吧，凱莉，看，看
Come on, Carrie Look, look
我的懷疑是對的，
My suspicions were right,
我的朋友，你有閱讀障礙
and you, my friend, are dyslexic
行
Okay
好吧，那只是意味著我有問題
Okay, so that just means I'm having problems
閱讀和寫作，對吧？
with my reading and my writing, right?
是的，但是你也有計算障礙
Yep, but you also have dyscalculia
椎間盤突出症...我甚至不知道怎麼發音
Discalcu... I don't even know how to pronounce that
基本上，這就像誦讀困難症，但與數學有關
Basically, it's like dyslexia but with math
這就是我得到的
That's what I got
我就知道
I knew it
既然你這麼說，那就有道理了
Now that you say it, it makes sense
如果你帶我去餐館
If you take me to a restaurant
你說，泰迪，留下小費，
and you say, Teddy, leave the tip,
我到處都是
I'm-I'm all over the place
這正是它
That's exactly what it is
我們做到了哦，我們還沒有做到
We did it Oh, we're not done
你也有加工障礙
You also have a processing disorder
我得了前列腺癌？
I got a touch of prostate cancer?
她一次也沒碰我的屁股
She didn't touch my ass one time
我說加工障礙。
I said processing disorder.
凱莉，如果你不幫我，
Carrie, if you're not going to help me,
那我們就浪費時間了
then we're wasting our time
向我解釋這是什麼東西
Explain to me what this stuff is
如果我有進展
If I got a proc
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
我不處理它
I'm not processing it
我什麼都沒處理
I didn't process none of that shit
你只是一種又大又漂亮的混合飲料
You are just one big, beautiful mixed drink
學習障礙
of learning disabilities
所以我不傻？
So I'm not dumb?
小子，我剛才說的時候還在玩呢
Boy, I was just playing when I said that earlier
沒有一個好老師會叫他們的學生啞巴
No good teacher would ever call their students dumb
行
Okay
那麼，我們如何修復它呢？讓我們談談解決方案
So, how do we fix it? Let's talk solution
嗯，你所擁有的沒有治癒的方法
Well, there's no cure for what you have
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God
我得了皰疹？
I got learning herpes?
男孩
Boy
哦，媽的
Oh, shit
沒有學習皰疹這樣的東西
There is no such thing as learning herpes
我渾身冒泡
I'm blistering up
這是因為我想
It's 'cause I'm trying to think
嘿，泰迪！嘿，麥克
Hey, Teddy! Hey, Mac
頭目嗨，夥計們
Ringleader Hi, guys
泰迪！是的，泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Yeah, Teddy! Teddy!
以傳統方式教學
Teaching the conventional way
只是不會為泰迪完成，
just isn't gonna get it done for Teddy,
所以我們要把它混在一起
so we're gonna mix it up
你在外面把它弄進來
You out here getting it in
怎麼了，嘉莉？你為什麼在這裡？
What's going on, Carrie? Why you in here?
你為什麼在戒指裡？怎麼回事？
Why you in the ring? What's going on?
泰迪，你的困難與焦點有關
Teddy, your difficulties are focus-related
嗯
Uh-huh
我的目標是消除那種思想上的喋喋不休
My goal is to remove that mind chatter
這樣你就可以獲得不受阻礙的神經通路
so you can achieve properly unencumbered neural pathways
這不是戒指
And this isn't a ring
它是一個六邊形
It's a hexagon
嗯。哦，是的
Huh. Oh, it is
是啊
Yeah, well
你為什麼脫掉鞋子？
Why you taking your shoes off?
這是某人的地毯嗎？
Is this somebody's carpet?
泰迪，81的平方根是多少？
Teddy, what's the square root of 81?
什麼？
What?
噢！噢！
Ow! Ow!
媽的！81的平方根是多少？
Shit! What's the square root of 81?
我不知道你做什麼...？
I don't know What you do...?
噢！嘉莉！81的平方根是多少？
Ow! Carrie! What's the square root of 81?
你打斷了我的胳膊！
You breaking my arm!
來吧，我們正在清除這些神經通路
Come on, we're clearing those neural pathways
不！停下來。嘿！
No! Stop. Hey!
你在做什麼？集中精神！
What you doing? Focus!
平方根！集中精神！
Square root! Focus!
我不知道！
I don't know!
哦，上帝！
Oh, God!
專心泰迪，專心
Concentrate Teddy, concentrate
來吧，泰迪，來吧
Come on, Teddy, come on
鈉鈉鈉鈉
Na na na-na na na
鈉鈉鈉鈉鈉鈉...
Na na-na na na na-na na na-na...
泰迪，你今天感覺如何？
How you feeling today, Teddy?
我感覺很好，凱莉，但是我感覺不到
I'm-I'm feeling fine, Carrie, but I ain't feeling
這個宮城先生，好嗎？
this Mr. Miyagi shit, okay?
比利時的首都是什麼？
What's the capital of Belgium?
呃
Uh
閒聊
waffles
什麼？快跑！
What? Run!
你不要逃避我
Don't you run from me
不要逃避我，不要。他太小了
Don't you run from me Don't. He's so little
比利時的首都是什麼？
What is the capital of Belgium?
我還沒吃早飯呢！我不知道！
I haven't eaten breakfast! I don't know!
這不是答案！
That is not the answer!
假裝你死了
Pretend you're dead
哦！哦！回來！
Oh! Oh! Get back here!
泰迪，集中注意力
Teddy, focus
集中精神，我們開始吧
Concentrate Let's do it
哦，告訴你我所有最深、最黑暗的秘密...
Ooh, tell you all my deepest, darkest secrets...
水包括...？
Water is comprised of...?
走吧，泰迪，你拿到了，泰迪
Let's go, Teddy You got this, Teddy
雨水。
Rain Rain.
等等，不，等等，等等
Wait, no. Wait, wait
我知道，我知道。嗯
I know it, I know it. Um
想
Think
集中精神！嗯...氦
Focus! Um... helium
不，不，不，不
No. No, no, no
氮氣。這是氮氣，對吧？
Nitrogen. It's nitrogen, right?
你最好把它弄對，這是一種氣體
You better get it right It's a gas
什麼？這是一種氣體！
What? It's a gas!
天啊！
Jesus Christ!
給我答案！
Give me the answer!
說出來！
Say it!
給我該死的答案
Give me the damn answer
告訴我！
Tell me!
這是兩部分氫，
It's two part hydrogen,
一部分...任何人
one part... one
一部分氧氣
one part oxygen
是的！再說一遍
Yes! Say that again
他說了別讓他再說了
He said it Don't make him say it again
我說了兩部分氫，
I said two part hydrogen,
一部分氧氣
one part oxygen
泰迪，沒錯
Teddy, that's right
你說得對什麼？
You got it right What?
這是正確的答案
That's the correct answer
我說得對
I got it right
你說得對，泰迪
You got it right, Teddy
是的。是
Yeah. Yes
是的！
Yes!
對我們所有人來說，這是多麼重要的一天
What a big day for all of us
我真不敢相信我真的
I can't believe that I actually
什麼？
What?
那是什麼味道？那是什麼？
What is that smell? What is that?
哦，現在，那是一種氣體
Oh, now, that's a gas
你撞了我的臉，汽車...？
You bust ass in my face, Car...?
甲烷
Methane
它在我嘴裡
It's in my mouth
你把我的嘴唇都弄裂了
You got my lips all chapped and shit
這不是什麼教育
This ain't no type of education
這是化學戰
This is chemical warfare
空投給你
AirDrop it to you
是
Yeah
特裡薩，怎麼了？
Theresa, what's wrong?
哦
Oh
我只是這一切進行得太快了
I just this all went so fast
我不想學校停課
I don't want school to end
行
Okay
好吧，你可以和我一起上大學
Well, you can come to college with me
什麼？你要去嗎？嗯
What? You're going? Mm-hmm
我真為你高興
I'm so happy for you
你什麼時候決定的？
When did you decide?
好吧，不要誤會，
Well, don't take this the wrong way,
但是和你們在一起把我嚇壞了
but hanging out with you guys scared the shit out of me
所以我想我會
So I think I'm gonna I think I'm gonna
用我的生命做點什麼
do something with my life
太棒了
That's wonderful
我現在可以看到你穿著最可愛的衣服
I can just see you now in the cutest outfit
穿過廣場的迷你裙
little miniskirt walking through the quad
你緊緊抓住你的哲學論文
You're clutching onto your philosophy thesis
但是當你上課的時候，教授被吹走了
But when you get to class, the professor is blown away
是啊
by how brilliant it is Yeah
所以他抓住你，你可以
So he grabs onto you, and you can
摸摸他靠著你的大腿
feel him up against your thigh
呃不是以性的方式，
Uh Not in a sexual way,
但不是以性的方式，你知道嗎？
but not not in a sexual way, you know?
他看起來奇怪地像布魯諾·火星
And he looks strangely like Bruno Mars
儘管他是超級學者，
Even though he's super academic,
他有時穿粉紅色的外套
he wears, like, pink blazers sometimes
好吧，你仍然可以上大學
Well, you can still go to college and do
其他的東西
that other stuff
我？大學？
Me? College?
哦，不，蘭迪不讓我去
Oh, no Randy wouldn't let me
去你媽的蘭迪。你可以做你想做的任何事情
Screw Randy. You can do whatever you want to do
你不認識蘭迪
You don't know Randy
為什麼你不能像，嘿，蘭迪
Why can't you just be like, Hey, Randy
我想做這個交易。
I want to do this Deal with it.
好吧！
Okay!
夜校學生
Night school people
最後一堂課，最後一次演示
Last class, final demonstration
凱莉，拜託，別再學習了
Carrie, please, no more learning
我的大腦已經滿負荷了
My brain is at capacity
我想成為一名牙科醫生，
I want to be a dental hy-enist,
不是埃隆·馬斯克或斯蒂芬·霍金
not Elon Musk or Stephen Hawking
好吧，路易斯
Well, okay, Luis
我就在你身邊
I'm right there with you
哈！
Ha!
哦，不
Oh, no
這是另一個科學實驗嗎？
Is this another science experiment?
哦，不，這是慶祝，巨無霸
Oh, no, this is a celebration, Big Mac
哦，是的。你們去過
Oh, yeah. You guys been
拚命幹活
working your asses off
嘿！媽的！
Hey! Shit!
哦，我很抱歉，鮑比
Oh, I'm so sorry, Bobby
不，那很酷，我要做我自己
No, that's cool I'm gonna make me
上鎖後沖廁所，寶貝
some toilet punch after lockdown, baby
你們都聽到音樂了嗎？
Y'all-y'all hear that music?
是啊，哦，是啊
Yeah Oh, yeah
哦，你知道嗎，今天是舞會之夜
Oh, you know what, it's prom night
你們去舞會了嗎？
You guys go to prom?
不，我在少管所真的嗎？
No, I was in juvie Really?
我帶著一個嬰兒回家
I was home with an infant
這是個信號，夥計們
This is a sign, guys
什麼？是的，我們一直在努力工作
What? Yeah, we've been working hard
我們應該釋放一些蒸汽
We should let some steam off
我們為什麼不去舞會？
Why don't we go to the prom?
你知道嗎？下課
You know what? Class dismissed
我們去搖那個屁股吧
Let's go shake that ass
我們去舞會吧，寶貝！我們去舞會吧！
Let's go to prom, baby! Let's go to prom!
哦，我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
只是遊戲的奴隸，我就像一隻鳥...
Just a slave to the game, I'm like a bird...
怎麼回事，特裡薩？
What the hell, Theresa?
我一直在外面按喇叭
I've been outside honking
大約15分鐘
for like 15 minutes
我覺得我可以突破天花板
I feel like I can break through the ceiling
所以我找到了一個沒有遺漏任何節奏的地方
So I find myself a place without missing a beat
他們給我買飲料
Where they buy me a drink
一個我可以自由跳舞的地方
A place where I can dance like I'm free
不要這樣對我說話
Don't talk to me like that
我會跳舞，直到這些鎖鏈落下...
I'll dance until these chains fall...
我是你妻子，我不是你媽媽，
I'm your wife I'm not your mommy,
我不是你的清潔工
and I'm not your house cleaner
當我拿到GED時，我會追求我的夢想，
And when I get my GED, I'm gonna pursue my dreams,
我需要你的支持
and I'm gonna need your support
此外，我想定期做愛
And also, I want to have sex on a regular basis
哦，嗯！
Oh Mmm!
我的意思是，像，古怪的性行為
I mean, like, kinky sex
比如，不要做嬰兒性愛，
Like, not make-a-baby sex,
但是45分鐘的性愛
but 45-minute sex
比如，五十度灰色性愛
Like, Fifty Shades of Grey sex
嗯？
Hmm?
我要你像核桃一樣咬我的屁股
I want you to crack my butt like a walnut
我說清楚了嗎？！
Do I make myself clear?!
好吧，好吧
Okay, okay
我很抱歉，寶貝
I'm so sorry, babe
我認為你是一個瘋狂的搖滾明星
I think you're a freakin' rock star
從你剛才對我說的話來判斷，
And judging by what you just said to me,
我迫不及待想成為你的色情明星
I can't wait to be your porn star
驚歎聲
Whoa
好吧，你們，
All right, y'all,
今晚我們在這裡開派對！
we got the party up in here tonight!
那是一批乾淨的
That's a clean batch
我希望這一拳能一直打下去
I want this punch to stay that way
整晚都在檢查
Gonna be checking throughout the night
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
對不起。這支舞只供學生跳
Excuse me. This dance is for students only
這是我的夜校課，
Well, this is my night school class,
他們是這裡的學生
and they are students here
好吧，技術上，技術上，你還是
Okay, well, technically, technically, you're still
所以，卡特小姐，
on school hours, so, Miss Carter,
請回到你的教室
please return to your classroom
好吧，我們要花我們的上課時間
Well, we gonna spend our class hours
在健身房，在聚會上，嘉莉
in the gym, at the party Carrie
讓開，婊子。快走！
So get out of the way, bitch. Move!
我不能允許這個她抓住你了。她抓住你了
I can't allow this She got you. She got you
夥計，你為什麼老是提起那個拉-拉，夥計？
Man, why you always about that rah-rah, man?
我會讓這一切發生
I'll allow this I'll allow this to happen
不過，我們只是想感受一下氣氛
We just trying to get a vibe, though
好吧，皮埃蒙特高中，
All right, Piedmont High,
給夜校的工作人員騰出地方！
make room for the night school crew!
一，二，三，呃！
One, two, three, uh!
我的孩子不會亂來...
My baby don't mess around...
小心，小心，小心！
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
這一點我是肯定的
And this I know for sure
大家，來吧！
Everybody, come on!
呃！
Uh!
感謝上帝，感謝爸爸媽媽堅持在一起...
Thank God for Mom and Dad for sticking to together...
哦，C小姐會殺了他們的！
Oh, Miss C gonna kill 'em!
是啊！嗯！
Yeah! Huh!
嘿，你好
Hey ya
是啊！
Yeah!
嘿，你好
Hey ya
嘿，你是骨盆，骨盆，骨盆
Hey ya Pelvic, pelvic, pelvic
嘿，你好
Hey ya
我們開始，呃，搖搖它，搖搖它
Here we go, uh, shake it, shake-shake it
搖，搖，搖
Shake it, shake-shake it
搖晃它，搖晃它，搖晃它，像這樣搖晃它
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it like
寶麗來照片
A Polaroid picture
搖，搖，搖
Shake it, shake it, shake it
你知道該怎麼做嗎
You know what to do
搖搖，搖搖，搖搖
Shake it, shake it, sh-sh-shake it
你知道該怎麼做嗎
You know what to do
嘿，你好
Hey ya
哦，哦
Oh, oh
嘿，你去吧，特裡薩！
Hey ya Go, Theresa!
哦，哦
Oh, oh
嘿，你好
Hey ya
哦，哦，她在打瞌睡！她在打瞌睡！
Oh, oh She's twerking! She's twerking!
嘿，你好，她在打瞌睡！
Hey ya She's twerking!
走吧，T！敲碎我的核桃！
Go, T! Crack my walnut!
那不是給孩子的，特裡薩！
That's not for kids, Theresa!
哦，哦，去吧，T！
Oh, oh Go, T!
嘿，你好
Hey ya
哦，哦
Ooh, ooh
Oh, oh
嘿，嘿
Hey, hey
夢是我活著的全部
The dream is all that keeps me alive
不管需要什麼
No matter what it takes
你知道我會一直戰鬥下去
You know I'm always gonna keep on fighting
我在戰鬥
I'm fighting
我永遠不會放棄夢想
I'm never gonna let the dream go
我會一直帶著這個
I'll take this all the way
沒人會停止做夢的no one ' s ever，ever will stop the dream
Nobody's ever, ever gonna stop el sueno
啊，啊，啊
Ah, ah, ah
沒有沙漠，沒有蛇會帶我下去
No desert, no snake gonna take me down
帶我下去
Take me down
等等，甜心，誰在看孩子們？
Wait, s-sweetheart, who-who's watching the kids?
我有保險
I got it covered
她說，我想成為一名空姐。
She said, I want to be a flight attendant.
你看到了嗎？
You see?
我想從一個地方走到另一個地方
I want to go from place to place
這就像去...
It'd be like going...
你們都在聽嗎？
Is y'all little bitches listening?
你知道，凱莉，你太不可思議了
You know, Carrie, you are incredible
我是認真的
I'm serious
從來沒有老師
There's never been a teacher
相信我和你一樣
that believe in me the way that you do
泰迪，我能說什麼？
Teddy, what can I say?
你在這麼短的時間里長得這麼大
You've grown so much in such a short period of time
如果你跟上所有的東西
And if you keep up with all the stuff
我們一直在做的事情，你已經在路上了
that we've been doing, you are well on your way
我只是
I'm just
我真的，真的為你驕傲
I'm really, really proud of you
你知道，凱莉，呃
You know, Carrie, uh
過去的幾周令人驚訝
these past few weeks have been amazing
我的意思是，我們的化學，不言而喻，
I mean, our chemistry, it goes without saying,
它很結實
it's strong
我感覺到了。我知道你也是
I sense it. I know you do, too
但是像這些時刻一樣神奇
But as magical as these moments
可能是
that we've been having may be
傻瓜，我是同性戀
Fool, I'm gay
我不想玩
I'm not trying to play
現在，我不是說我不是怪胎，
Now, I'm not saying I ain't no freak,
因為我會把它落在你身上
cause I'd drop it off on you
我是女同性戀
I'm a lesbian
如果你想繼續演戲，你可以
If you want to pursue acting, you can
不，我是同性戀
No, I'm gay
再說一遍。聽起來你好像說你是同性戀
Say that again. It sound like you said you're gay
我是同性戀
I'm gay
我喜歡女人
I like women
你確定？因為我越來越
Are you sure? Because I'm getting
一種完全不同的氛圍哦，不！
a whole different vibe Oh, hell no!
我很確定哦，上帝
I'm pretty sure Oh, God
泰迪？
Teddy?
左邊的那個是你喜歡的類型嗎？
Is the, is the one on the left your type?
呃，穿緊身衣的那個是
Uh-uh, the one in the tight dress is
媽的，那是我的
Shit, that's mine
嘿
Hey
他們去了
There they go
在這裡幹嗎？
What are you doing here?
嗯？
Huh?
你在高中畢業舞會上做什麼？
What are you doing at a high school prom?
什麼...寶貝，你在這裡幹什麼？
What, uh... what-what are you doing here, babe?
為什麼是你...你為什麼在這裡？
Why you... why you here?
帕特斯基校長對我們感興趣
Principal Patowsky is interested in us
重新設計學校，所以他讓我們停下來
redesigning the school, so he asked us to stop by
哦，他做到了，嗯？
Oh, he did, huh?
打得好，斯圖爾特
Well played, Stewart
你們倆認識嗎？
You two know each other?
問斯圖爾特
Ask Stewart
嗯，是的，我們一起上高中
Uh, yes, we went to high school together
我想我在第一次會議上提到過這一點
I think I mentioned that at our first meeting
不，不，你沒有
No. No, you didn't
泰迪，我很困惑
Teddy, I am so confused
你為什麼在這裡？她是誰？
Why are you here? And who is she?
我可以解釋這不是它的樣子
I can explain It ain't what it look like
我和一群孩子在這裡，
I'm in here with a bunch of kids,
穿著街頭服裝
dressed in street clothes
然後記得我炸了燒烤小屋
Then remember I blew out the, uh, Barbecue Shack
火把我從那東西裡救了出來
Fire took me out of that thing
現在我的擋風玻璃被弄髒了
And now my windshield was-was messed
讓我把車搞砸了
got me messed up about the car
我的剎車失靈了，因為我倒車了，嗯
My brakes ain't working, 'cause I backed into this, um
她是同性戀。她甚至沒有
She gay. She ain't even
她甚至對我不感興趣
She ain't even interested in me
因此...因此
So... so
該死的
Goddamn it
elizabeth的暱稱
Lisa
現在不行。不是現在，等等
Not now. Not now Wait
elizabeth的暱稱
Lisa
好吧，麗莎
Okay, Lisa
麗莎，麗莎
Lisa, Lisa
麗莎，你能聽嗎？
Lisa, can you listen, please?
麗莎，請聽著
Lisa, please just listen
什麼？泰迪，你想說什麼？
What? What are you gonna say, Teddy?
我是高中輟學生
I'm a high school dropout
好嗎？裡面那個女人，
Okay? That woman in there,
凱莉，那是我的夜校老師
Carrie that's my night school teacher
這就是我這些晚上一直在做的事情
That's what I've been doing all these evenings
我一直在學習以獲得我的GED
I've been studying to get my GED
這樣我就能在馬文家找到一份工作
so that I can get a job at Marvin's
所以你現在不在那裡工作？
So you don't work there now?
我沒有
I don't
我還沒有在那裡工作
I don't work there yet
現在我在一家快餐店工作
Right now I work at a fast food restaurant
叫做基督教雞，
called Christian Chicken,
因為某種原因，雞肉是基督教的
where the chicken is Christian for some reason
哦，等等。麗莎，
Oh, wait. L-Lisa,
麗莎，麗莎，讓我來
Lisa, Lisa, let me just
在你評判他之前，先說這個
say this before you judge him
這不是普通雞
It ain't that average chicken
這不是一樣的快餐
It's not the same fast food
你從這些小兜帽上得到的
that you be getting from these other little hood spots
它有味道...我不知道他們是否使用針頭，
It's got the flavor... I don't know if they use a needle,
但是他們得到了傑倫、傑倫、傑倫的味道！
but they get the flavor Jaylen, Jaylen, Jaylen!
你怎麼知道我的名字？
How do you know my name?
我的黑鬼一直在班上談論你
My nigga be talking about you in the class all the time
他說你很壞我不知道你那麼壞
He said you was bad I didn't know you was that bad
我們是泰迪的同學，我是特裡薩
We're Teddy's classmates I'm Theresa
那是傑倫、米拉、麥肯齊和路易斯·嘿
That's Jaylen, Mila, Mackenzie, and Luis Hey
你記得我嗎？實際上我是服務員
You remember me? I-I was actually the waiter
在餐館裡，泰迪拔掉了他所有的陰毛，
at the restaurant when Teddy pulled all of his pubes,
然後...他把它們放在芝士蛋糕裡
and then... and he put 'em in the cheesecake
擺脫支付
to get out of paying
現在我們是最好的朋友
Now we're best friends
謝謝你的誠實
Thank you for your honesty
誠實
Honesty
我知道
I know
這是一個很大的挑戰
that this is a lot to take in
真的嗎？
Really?
但是如果你讓我解釋一下
But if you let me explain
不，如果你只是...如果你讓我解釋
No If you just... if you let me explain
不，泰迪，我聽完你的解釋了
No, Teddy, I'm done with your explanations
你對我撒謊了
You lied to me about everything
為什麼？
Why?
給我留下深刻印象？
To impress me?
泰迪，我自己賺錢
Teddy, I make my own money
你以為我在乎你開哪種車
You think I care about what kind of car you drive
或者你戴什麼樣的手錶？
or what kind of watch you have on?
那不是我
That's not me
如果你這麼想，那你就不認識我了
If you think that, then you don't know me
這不是真的
That's not true
如果你不認識我，
If you don't know me,
那你就不能真正愛我
then you couldn't truly love me
這不是真的，麗莎
That's not true, Lisa
今晚不要回到公寓
Don't come back to the apartment tonight
嗯，也許你可以和你的夜校朋友呆在一起
Well, maybe you could stay with your night school friend
也許她會有一些用處
Maybe she'd have some use for this
這可能是假的，對吧？
It's probably fake, right?
elizabeth的暱稱
Lisa
列斯
Lis
麗莎！
Lisa!
我切掉了外殼，
I cut the crust off,
你喜歡它嗎
just how you like it
謝謝，媽
Thanks, Ma
你沒有認真跳過GED考試吧？
You're not seriously skipping that GED test, are you?
是
Yeah
我是說，我是在為麗莎做這些事情
I mean, I was doing all that stuff for Lisa
如果她不在，那又有什麼意義呢？
If she's not around, then what's the point?
我可憐的孩子，我感覺很糟糕
My poor baby, I feel terrible
哦，格拉迪絲，現在，別再溺愛這個男孩了
Oh, Gladys, now, stop coddling this boy
西奧多，
You know, Theodore,
你是個成年人
you're a grown-ass man
你需要振作起來
You need to get your shit together
我知道，爸爸
I know, Dad
我的意思是，你說你有閱讀障礙，
I mean, you say you got dyslexia,
發育障礙。
dyscoglia.
計算障礙
Dyscalculia
不管你怎麼說
However you say it
問題是你不誠實
The issue is you're dishonest
我不怪那個女孩拋棄了你
I don't blame that girl for dumping you
傑拉爾德，夠了
Now, Gerald, that is enough Uh-huh
你知道，也許你是對的
You know, maybe you're right
也許我活該
Maybe I do deserve it
你覺得呢？
You think?
我在諷刺你
I was being sarcastic
我會幫你準備好床的，寶貝
I'll get your bed ready, baby
你想吃點什麼嗎？
Would you like a tuck-in?
是的，請
Yes, please
謝謝你，媽媽
Thank you, Mom
給你什麼，親愛的
Anything for you, darling
我失敗了
I failed
作為父親，我失敗了
I failed as a father
插兜？
A tuck-in?
哦，我的天啊，他為什麼這樣上公共汽車？
Oh, my gosh, why'd he come on the bus like that?
我不知道他沒有朋友
I don't know He ain't got no friends
有什麼問題嗎？
What's the problem?
基督教雞！
Christian Chicken!
叫我可憐的先生
Call me Mr. Pitiful
如果你喜歡雞肉，按一下喇叭
Honk once if you love chicken
如果你愛上帝，按兩下喇叭
Honk twice if you love the Lord
如果你願意，來拿你的雞肉
Come and get your chicken if you
準備開始獲勝
ready to start winning
嘿
Hey
賣完了！
Sellout!
什麼？
What?
你賣完了，夥計
You a sellout, man
兄弟，我只是想誠實的生活
Brother, I'm just trying to make an honest living
你為什麼不離開我？
Why don't you get off my back?
那就去郵局找份工作吧
Go get a job at the post office, then
滾出去什麼？再說一遍！
Get your ass up out of here What? Say it again!
來吧，夥計！
Come on, man!
繼續吧
Go ahead with that
保持清醒，布拉赫
Stay woke, brah
是啊，我看到你吃了雞肉，你這個狗娘養的
Yeah, well, I see you ate the chicken, you son of a bitch
所以，這就是現在的情況，嗯？
So, this is what it's come to, huh?
你有膽量，夥計
You got some nerve, man
泰迪，看
Teddy, look
我是來道歉的
I came here to apologize
我休息了
I'm on my break
我沒有時間看這個泰迪，請聽著
I ain't got time for this Teddy, please, just listen
我不想聽你說什麼，夥計
I don't want to hear nothing you got to say, man
不，請聽我說
No, please just listen to me
我沒有什麼要對你說的
I don't have nothing to say to you
我只是...嗯，我有話要對你說，好嗎？
I just... well, I have something to say to you, okay?
什麼？什麼？給我30秒，好嗎？
What? What? Give me 30 seconds, okay?
30 seconds. Go
聽著，當我們在高中的時候，
Listen, when-when we were in high school,
你擁有了我想要的一切
you had everything that I wanted
你還有28秒
You got 28 seconds left
我只有分數
I had grades That's all I had
你有運動，朋友，女孩
You-you had sports, friends, girls
我吸了所有這些
I sucked at all that
當我得到第一手工作時，我27歲
I was 27 when I got my first hand job
你在一號，但在我離開之前，
You're at one, but before I before I walk away,
我想告訴你這很難過
I want to tell you that's sad
這是我的觀點，我不在乎
That's my point I don't care
你為什麼告訴我？我的觀點是
Why are you telling me? My point is
我是一個晚熟的人，我絕望而悲傷，
I was a late bloomer, and I was desperate and sad,
我責怪你
and I blamed you
那天晚上，
And the other night,
當我報復的時候，感覺很糟糕
when I got my revenge, it felt awful
我接受教育是為了有所作為
I got into education to make a difference
在人們的生活中，不要毀掉他們
in people's lives, not to ruin them
還有，
Also,
我告訴斯圖爾特我打了他的屁股
I told Stewart here I'd beat his ass
如果他沒有來道歉
if he didn't come and apologize
那是真的那是一部分
That is true That was a part
一部分，一小部分
part of it, a small part
好吧，你們知道嗎，夥計們？
Okay, you know what, guys?
我欣賞整個課後特殊時刻
I appreciate the whole after-school special moment
但是要明白我沒事
But understand that I am okay
我是我應該去的地方
I am where I'm supposed to be
好嗎？你的命運是工作
All right? Your destiny is to work
在脫衣舞俱樂部旁邊的快餐店？
at a fast food joint next to a strip club?
是的。好吧，如果我站在正確的位置
Yes. All right, if I stand in the right spot
在這個停車場，我能聞到可可脂的味道
in this parking lot, I can smell cocoa butter
和炸雞
and fried chicken at the same time
我不知道你們的情況，但這對我來說是一場勝利
And I don't know about you guys, but that's a win for me
泰迪，聽我說。泰德不是泰迪，聽著。
Teddy, l-listen to me. Ted Ain't no Teddy, listen.
你知道我不會通過考試的，
You know I wasn't gonna pass that test,
所以不要坐在這裡，表現得像
so don't sit here and act like
這不會是不同的故事
it wasn't gonna be a different story
不要表現得像你不想要的那樣
And don't act like you don't want
終於可以說我是啞巴了
to be able to finally say that I'm dumb
不，你沒有
No, you're not
你終於可以說了，斯圖，說吧
You can finally say it, Stew Say it
泰迪
Teddy
你是很多東西
you are a lot of things
騙子
A hustler
A liar
你很矮
You're very short
瘋狂大聲，嗯
Mad loud, too Mmm
但是你不傻
But you are not dumb
現在，你穿的這套衣服真蠢
Now, this suit you got on is dumb as hell
我責備你...？
I rebuke you You...?
責備。我責備你！
Rebuke. I rebuke you!
男孩...給我這個我要去工作的東西
Boy... give me this thing I'm going to work
現在，讓我回到你在做什麼？
Now, let me go back to What you doing?
你在做什麼，夥計？脫下這套衣服，
What you doing, man? Take this suit off,
你要參加這個測試不，不，不，不，不，不，不
and you gonna take this test No, no, no, no, no, no, no
不，讓我們用我們的話來說，你要參加這次考試嗎
No, let's use our words You gonna take this test
好了，過來你知道嗎？
All right, come here You know what?
你在做什麼？她有一條腰帶
What you doing? She has a belt
她有皮帶！
She's got a belt!
你要脫下這套衣服嘿！
You gonna take this suit off Hey!
呃，夥計們，夥計們，夥計們，夥計們
Uh, guys, guys, guys, guys
你停下！你呆在那裡！放開我！
You stop! You stay there! Get off me!
這會傷害我，而不是傷害你
It's gonna hurt me more than it's gonna hurt you
哦，上帝，我不能參與其中
Oh, God, I can't be a part of this
要撕了你的屁股！
Gonna tear your ass up!
好吧，這似乎是一件黑色的事情，
Okay, this seems like a black thing,
所以我- -我只是想給我們點些食物
so I-I'm just gonna order us some food
好吧！好吧！現在，聽我說
All right! All right! Now, listen to me
你在聽我說嗎？是
You listening to me? Yes
現在，你工作太辛苦了
Now, you have worked too hard to be
穿著該死的雞服在這裡跑來跑去
running around here in a damn holy chicken suit
好嗎？是
Okay? Yes
現在，要麼你上車
Now, either you get in the car
你參加了測試，
and you take that test,
否則我繼續嫩化你的屁股！
or I continue to tenderize your ass!
你的選擇
Your choice
準備好了嗎？祝你們好運
Are you ready? Good luck, guys
是的，我回來了
Yeah I'm back
嘿，凱莉
Hey, Carrie
泰迪！哦，泰迪回來了
Teddy! Aw, Teddy's back
很高興見到你，兄弟，怎麼了，泰德？
Good to see you, bro What's up, Ted?
嘿，泰迪·泰迪！泰迪！
Hey, Teddy Teddy! Teddy!
是的！
Yes!
怎麼了，國王？
What up, king?
來吧，夥計
Come on, man
讓我們這樣做
Let's do this
我們的英雄回來了
Our hero returns
好吧。我們完成了
Okay. We're complete
讓我們打開這些電腦
So let's turn on those computers
贏得這個東西
and ace this thing
去
Go
好吧，機器人
Okay, robot
你今天向上帝鞠躬
You bowing down to a god today
祝大家好運
Good luck, everybody
啊
Ah
來吧，泰迪
Come on, Teddy
集中
Focus
集中注意
Concentrate
別再喋喋不休了
Get rid of that mind chatter
來吧。集中
Come on. Focus
集中精神！哦，上帝！
Focus! Oh, God!
專注你最好把它做對
Focus You better get it right
集中，集中，集中！
Focus, focus, focus!
是啊！
Yeah!
噓
Shh
好了，大家冷靜下來，好嗎？
Okay, everybody calm down, all right?
結果將在一分鐘後上線
The results will be in online in just a minute
如果你超過145歲，你就通過了她是對的
If you get over 145, you pass She's right
好吧，你努力工作，就會得到回報
All right, you do the hard work, you get rewarded for it
沒必要驚慌
No need to panic
嘿，嘿，嘿，結果剛剛出來
Hey, hey, hey The results just came in
哦，媽的哦，我的天啊。呃
Oh, shit Oh, my gosh. Uh
我通過了。我有一輛146！
I passed. I got a 146!
146! Nice! Yeah!
前進的道路是的！
Way to go Yes!
管理層，我來了，寶貝！
Management, here I come, baby!
他活該
He deserved that
哦！
Oh!
游大！
Swim big!
我再也不用做家務了
I don't have to do housework anymore
我通過了！耶！鮑比通過了
I passed! Yay! Bobby passed
鮑比通過了，你們都通過了，鮑比
Bobby passed, y'all Yes, Bobby
165, B!
走吧，夥計
Way to go, man
我要上大學了！
I'm going to college Yeah!
她準備好了！-嘿！為你驕傲，孩子
She ready! - Hey! Proud of you, kiddo
為你驕傲，孩子
Proud of you, kiddo
夥計們。各位
Guys. Guys
我會成為一名牙科醫生
I'm I'm gonna be a dental hy-enist
衛生員。他說衛生專家。
Hygienist. He's saying hygienist.
我會成為一名牙科醫生
I'm gonna be a dental hy-enist
是的。這對你有好處，夥計
Yes. It's good for you, man
你們準備好了嗎？
Y'all ready for this?
什麼？傑伊得了146分！
What? Jay got a 146!
傑伊得了該死的146分！
Jay got a damn 146!
和你一樣，媽媽！是啊！是啊！
Same as you, fam! Yeah! Yeah!
是啊！我們贏了！為你們感到驕傲
Yeah! We won this! Proud of you guys
你說了你有什麼？
You said it What you got?
你有什麼？來吧，泰迪
What you got? Come on, Teddy
來吧，泰迪
Come on, Teddy
我不能。我不能檢查它
I can't. I can't check it
這裡，凱莉，這裡，你幫我檢查一下我的
Here, Carrie, here, you check mine for me
哦，上帝
Oh, God
我太緊張了，夥計
I'm too nervous, man
開始
Come on
天才水平
Genius level
沒錯
That's right
唷！
Whew!
泰迪，對不起
Teddy, I'm sorry
來吧，嘉莉現在不要玩了
Come on, Carrie Don't play right now
僅僅...告訴我比分
Just... just tell me the score
告訴我我得到了什麼
Tell me what I got
我不是在跟你開玩笑
I'm not joking with you this
你沒有通過
You didn't pass
我有117
I got a 117
對不起，泰迪
I'm sorry, Teddy
沒關係，你知道為什麼嗎？
It doesn't matter You know why?
因為這是一個小挫折
Because this is a this is a minor setback
為了一次重大的復出
for a major comeback
是的，我又要參加考試了，夥計們
Yes I'm-a take the test again, guys
沒錯。是的，你應該！
That's right. Yes You should!
我- a再考一次你再考一次！
I'm-a take the test again You take it again!
你又來了，沒錯
You're taking it again That's right
我說了我會再來一次！
I said I'm-a take it again!
哦，上帝，他在用他的聲音做那件事
Oh, God, he's doing that thing with his voice
是的，我知道我也聽到了
Yeah, I know I heard it, too
我再次參加考試！
I'm-a take the test again!
嘿，嘿
Hey, hey
有些人有時
Some people sometimes
他們認為他們需要收工...
They think they need to call it a day...
每個人都有相同的號碼嗎？
Is everybody getting the same number?
嘿，馬伕，是嗎？
Hey, Marv Yeah?
我失敗了
I failed
你考試不及格？
You failed the test?
但是我又拿了一次
But I'm-a take it again
這就是你來的原因？
That's why you stopped by?
從來沒有被抓過...
Ain't never been caught up...
我又失敗了
I failed again
是的，但是我現在又拿了
Yep, but I'm-a take it again now
我- -再來一次
I'm-a take it again
我是說我看到了我的未來...
I'm saying I see my future...
嘿，你們
Hey, y'all
我絕對沒有通過那個考試
I definitely didn't pass that one
我的意思是，有一整部分
I mean, there was a whole section
我甚至不明白
that I didn't even understand
不過，我要再來一次
I'm-a take it again, though
你確定他不只是啞巴？
You sure he's not just dumb?
新的測試結果
Well, the new test results
剛進來
just came in
我失敗了
I failed
等一下
Wait a minute
等等，我通過了
Wait, I passed
你什麼？
You what?
178那是大學，對吧？
A 178 That's, like, college, right?
我通過了
I passed
你通過了？
You passed?
嘿
Hey
我通過了！我通過了！
I passed! I passed!
你殺了它，兒子
You killed it, son
我做到了，夥計！我做到了！
I did it, man! I did it!
嘿，小心你的背部小心你的背部！
Hey, watch your back Watch your back!
哦，是啊！
Oh, yeah!
泰迪！泰迪！哇！
Teddy! Teddy! Whoa!
泰迪！泰迪！我通過了！
Teddy! Teddy! I passed!
泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Teddy!
謝謝你！謝謝你！
Thank you! Thank you!
我不配！
I don't deserve it!
我們，2018屆，代表一代人
We, the class of 2018, represent a generation
向前思考的能力，
of forward-thinking,
挑戰規則，無畏的領導者
rule-challenging, fearless leaders
讓我們從今天開始
Let us go forward from this day
充滿信心和勇氣
with confidence and with courage
當我們跨過這個階段時，讓我們用知識來做
As we cross this stage, let us do so with the knowledge
相信自己，沒有什麼是不可能的
that with faith in ourselves, nothing is impossible
謝謝你
Thank you
美麗動人的話語
Beautiful and inspiring words
謝謝你，米卡伊拉
Thank you, Mikayla
現在，在我們結束之前，
Now, before we conclude,
我相信你們中的一些人在想
I'm sure some of you are wondering
為什麼我們的舞台上有成年學生
why we have adult students with us onstage
你們都知道，
Well, as you all know,
我是一個創新者
I am an innovator
特立獨行的人
A maverick
我不玩遊戲
I don't play by the
所以我決定，
So I have decided,
皮埃蒙特歷史上第一次，
for the first time in Piedmont history,
邀請夜校畢業生
to invite our night school graduates
加入我們的長輩
to join our seniors
他們選出了自己的一個
They have elected one of their own
代表他們發言
to speak on their behalf
它非常自豪
It is with great pride
我介紹泰迪·沃克先生
that I introduce Mr. Teddy Walker
嘿，好吧
Hey, all right
是啊！你拿到了，泰迪
Yeah! You got this, Teddy
你有這個泰迪！泰迪！
You got this Teddy! Teddy!
泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Teddy!
泰迪！泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Teddy! Teddy!
泰迪！泰迪！
Teddy! Teddy!
泰迪！
Teddy!
呃，讓我先告訴你們
Uh, let me just start off by telling you guys
關於我的一些事情
a little something about me
我是泰迪·沃克，還有
I'm Teddy Walker, and
我是個騙子
I'm a liar
多年來，我一直在假裝是別人
For years, I've been pretending to be somebody else
我不是的人
Somebody that I'm not
我這樣做的原因是因為我感到羞愧
And my reason for doing that is because I was ashamed
很慚愧我沒有像我的同學一樣學習
Ashamed that I didn't learn like my classmates
很慚愧我不能參加考試
Ashamed that I couldn't take a test
很慚愧我讓我的家人和朋友失望了
Ashamed that I let my family and my friends down
我的意思是，我投入了太多的時間和精力去創造
I mean, I put so much time and energy into creating
這個假版本的泰迪·沃克
this fake version of Teddy Walker
我忘記了在學校學習的價值
that I forgot the value that went into learning in school
我說的是誠實
I'm talking about honesty
我在說接受你是誰
I'm talking about accepting who you are
直到我遇見
And it wasn't until I met
我驚人的夜校同學和
my amazing night school classmates and
一個真正相信我的老師
and a teacher that actually believed in me
我能夠接受我是誰
that I was able to accept who I was
作為一個帶著一船貨物的大嘴巴騙子
As a loudmouth hustler with a boatload
學習障礙
of learning disabilities
你知道，對你們中任何一個曾經掙扎過的人來說
You know, for any of you who may have struggled
麗莎第一次做對了。-嗨
to get it right the first time Lisa. - Hi
我是活生生的證據
that I am living proof
你可以在第二次機會把它集合起來
that you can get it together on a second chance
我的意思是，我有很多機會
I mean, I done had a lot of chances
嗯
Mm-hmm
因為我搞砸了很多
'Cause I messed up a lot
嗯
Mm-hmm
但是我到了另一邊
But I made it to the other side
我是說，見鬼，我們都有
I mean, hell, we all did
對吧，夜校的工作人員？
Ain't that right, night school crew?
是啊
Hell yeah
我們都有第二次機會
We all got second chances
還有我爸爸
And to my dad
他是...他對我很嚴厲
He was... he was tough on me
他說了一些事情，但是他說這些是出於愛
He said some things, but he said it out of love
爸爸，我知道你不是故意的
Dad, I know you ain't never mean it
當你過去說一些事情的時候
when you used to say some of the things
你以前說過的
that you used to say
你知道，你曾經說過這樣的話，
You know, you used to say stuff like,
我希望我沒有擁有你。
I wish I ain't never had you.
或者像，呃，
Or like, uh,
那是浪費精子。哦！
That was a waste of sperm. Oh!
哦，上帝，如果我可以的話
Oh Oh, God, if I could
把螺母拿回來。我記得你說過
get that nut back. I remember you said that
但是所有這些都是出於愛
But all that stuff was said out of love
來激勵和推動我
to motivate me and push me
你認為你做得不好，
And you thought you didn't do good,
但是現在看著我
but look at me now
一切皆有可能！
Anything is possible!
我做到了！
I did it!
是啊！萬歲！走吧，泰迪！
Yeah! Hurray! Go, Teddy!
嘿，爸爸
Hey, Dad
我做到了，爸爸！
I did it, Dad!
我告訴過你
I told you
我跟你說過什麼？
What'd I tell you?
好吧。行
Okay. Okay
是啊！
Yeah!
真不敢相信我會因為這該死的事下班
Can't believe I took off work for this shit
謝謝你們的花
Thank you, guys, for the flowers
看看上面寫著什麼
Look what it says
嘿！嗯，我確實需要這份工作
Hey! Well, I definitely need the work
我需要錢，所以，呃...那是泰迪
I need the money, so That's, uh... that's Teddy
你最後一次戀愛是什麼時候？
When's the last time you were in love?
我工作。我有工作。我在拯救生命好吧。行
I work. I have a job. I'm saving lives Okay. Okay
好吧。你熱愛你的工作，這是我喜歡做的
Okay. You love your job That's what I love to do
哦，他來了
Oh, there he is
我那聰明又笨的弟弟
My little, smart, dumb-ass brother
我為你感到驕傲
I'm so proud of you
哦，謝謝你是的
Oh, thank you Yes
很高興見到你很高興見到你
Good to see you Good to see you
謝謝你是的
Thank you Yes
啊。給我一些，夥計啊！祝賀
Ah. Give me some, man Ah! Congrats
謝謝你，老兄，我看起來怎麼樣？我看起來聰明嗎？
Thank you, man How do I look? Do I look smart?
你看起來不可思議讓我看看你聰明的臉
You look unbelievable Let me see your smart face
嗯，打吧。一，二，三
Hmm Hit it. One, two, three
給我看看這張聰明的臉
Show me the smart face
是的，這仍然很愚蠢，給我看
Yeah, it's still stupid Show it to me
就這樣。-我喜歡它好吧，那很好
That's it. - I love it Okay, that's fine
好吧。好吧，沒關係
Okay. All right That's all right
叫我
Call me
嘿
Hey
那是一篇漂亮的演講，泰迪
That was a beautiful speech, Teddy
那就是我愛上的人
That's the guy I fell in love with
那麼請允許我重新介紹我自己
Then allow me to reintroduce myself
我是泰迪·沃克
I'm Teddy Walker
我是高中輟學生
I'm a high school dropout
我在快餐店工作
I work at a fast food joint
我和媽媽住在一起
I live with my mom
我坐公共汽車
And I take the bus
但是我會喜歡的
But I would love
我絕對會喜歡的
I would absolutely love it
如果你讓我帶你去約會
if you would let me take you on a date
很高興見到你，泰迪·沃克
Nice to meet you, Teddy Walker
我想要那個
I'd like that
你必須為一切付出代價
You're gonna have to pay for everything
因為我沒錢
because I I don't have any money
哦，我想
Oh, I figured
我是說，就像沒錢一樣
I mean, like no money
我抓住你了
I got you
讓我們拍張照片
Let's do a photo
夜校照片
Night school photo
GED在三樓。準備好了嗎？
GED on three. You ready?
GED在三個一，二，三
GED on three One, two, three
GED！
GED!
嗯！嘿，你好
Huh! Hey ya
嘿，嘿，嘿！嘿！嘿！
Hey ya Hey! Hey! Hey!
嘿，嘿，嘿！
Hey, hey, hey!
這是怎麼回事？
What is going on?
該輪到你了，斯圖爾特
It's turn-up time, Stewart
這個
Well, this
我的房子證明了嗎
is my house Prove it
一，二，三，呃！
One, two, three, uh!
搖，搖，搖，搖
Shake it, shake-shake it, shake it
哦，哦
Oh, oh
搖，搖，搖
Shake it, shake it, shake it
像寶麗來照片一樣搖晃它
Shake it like a Polaroid picture
好吧，好吧，好吧
All right, all right, all right
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧
All right, all right, all right, all right
好吧，好吧，好吧
All right, all right, all right
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧
All right, all right, all right, all right
哦，哦
Oh, oh
i
I
爆炸性新聞字幕
Subtitles by explosiveskull
拍拍自己的背
Pat yourself on the back
你就是這麼做的
You just did that
拍拍自己的後背
Pat yourself on the back cause
在後面
On the back
你剛畢業
You just graduated
你需要休假
You need a vacation
謝謝你的耐心
Thanks for all your patience
舉起手來，因為我們成功了
Hands up 'cause we made it
舉起手來
Hands up
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh-oh, oh
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh-oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
舉起手來，因為你成功了
Put your hands up cause you made it
舉起手來
Hands up
首先，我成功了
First in the fam, I made it
第一
First
我差點沒成功
I almost failed it
我說的是糟糕的成績，你救不了我
I'm talkin' bad, bad grades, you couldn't save me
糟糕，糟糕
Bad, bad
每個老師都想耍我
Every teacher tried to play me
你
F you
是的，他們打我
Yeah, they play me
媽媽說這沒瘋，沒讓我擔心
Mama said it wasn't crazy, didn't faze me
根本
At all
現在你得付錢給我
Now you gotta pay me
我知道我整個母校可能都恨我
I know my whole alma mater probably hate me
那麼？
So?
現在，我靈活運用格萊美獎
Now I flex Grammys
他們都懷孕了，媽的，我坐賓利
They all pregnant, shit, I'm flyin' on a Bentley
當你選他們的時候，婊子
And when you picked 'em, bitch
你應該選我
You should've picked me
嘿，你剛畢業
Hey, you just graduated
你需要休假
You need a vacation
謝謝你的耐心
Thanks for all your patience
舉起手來，因為我們成功了
Hands up 'cause we made it
一，二，舉起手來
One, two, hands up
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh-oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
舉起手來，因為你成功了
Put your hands up cause you made it
舉起手來
Hands up
我不會回頭
I ain't lookin' back
當我走過那扇門時
When I walk through that door
我不會回來了
I ain't comin' back
脫掉我的帽子和長袍，然後我扔掉我的帽子
Take my cap and gown off, then I throw my hat
喔！
Whoo!
因為是他幹的
'Cause he did that
我的兄弟
My dawg
吻我的嘴，因為該是時候了
Kiss my crush in the mouth cause it's 'bout time
我希望你關心你的錢，因為我關心我的錢
I hope you're all about your money, 'cause I'm 'bout mine
支票
Check
春假小姐
Miss spring break
請不要試圖成為我的朋友，因為太晚了
Please don't try to be my friend, 'cause it's too late
你認為我是- -讓你像個傻瓜一樣耍我？
You think I'm-a let you play me like a dumb-ass?
從不
Never
上數學課
Up in math class
我知道沒有保護的性行為並不壞
I learned unprotected sex ain't so bad
嗯
Mmm
有些沒通過，謝天謝地
Some didn't pass, thank God
你剛畢業
You just graduated
你需要休假
You need a vacation
謝謝你的耐心
Thanks for all your patience
舉起手來，因為我們成功了
Hands up 'cause we made it
舉起手來，舉起手來
Hands up, hands up
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
舉起手來，因為你成功了
Put your hands up cause you made it
舉起手來
Hands up
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
謝謝你的耐心
Thank you for your patience
大家都去
Everyone go
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
舉起手來，因為你成功了
Put your hands up cause you made it
舉起手來
Hands up
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
謝謝你的耐心
Thank you for your patience
大家都去
Everyone go
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh-oh, oh, oh, oh
你剛畢業
You just graduated
舉起手來，因為你成功了
Put your hands up cause you made it
舉起手來
Hands up
沒人會停止做夢的no one ' s ever，ever will stop the dream
Nobody's ever, ever gonna stop el sueno
啊，啊，啊
Ah, ah, ah
沒有沙漠，沒有蛇會帶我下去
No desert, no snake gonna take me down
帶我下去，不行
Take me down, no way
沒人會停止做夢的no one ' s ever，ever will stop the dream
Nobody's ever, ever gonna stop el sueno
啊，啊，啊
Ah, ah, ah
我總是會找到生存的力量
I'm always gonna find the strength to survive
為了生存
To survive
睡眠，睡眠
El sueno, el sueno
睡眠，睡眠，睡眠
El sueno, el sueno, el sueno
我活在夢裡
I'm living the dream
外面忙著賺錢
Out here busy gettin' money
我有兩個糟糕的數字
I got two bad countin' for me
我想在山上建一棟七位數的房子
I want a seven-digit house on the hill
我做得很好！
I'm-a do it good!
你知道我保持顫音
You know I keep it trill
他們叫我小椰子，我在洛杉磯玩
They call me Young Coconut, I'm en la playa
普拉亞！
Playa!
因為我永遠不會退休
'Cause I'm never gonna retire
哦，該死的不！
Oh, hell no!
我在這些街道上打車，我和我的偷窺者們在一起
I Uber in these streets, I'm wildin' with my peeps
我的座位上有個脫衣舞女
I got a stripper on my seat
因為她知道
'Cause she know
傑伊帶來了那個節拍
Jay brought that beat
我的夢想
El sueno
沒人會停止做夢的no one ' s ever，ever will stop the dream
Nobody's ever, ever gonna stop el sueno
啊，啊，啊
Ah, ah, ah
沒有沙漠，沒有蛇會帶我下去
No desert, no snake gonna take me down
帶我下去，不行
Take me down, no way
沒人會停止做夢的no one ' s ever，ever will stop the dream
Nobody's ever, ever gonna stop el sueno
啊，啊，啊
Ah, ah, ah
我總是會找到生存的力量
I'm always gonna find the strength to survive
夢！夢！
!El sueno!